me on static in the cathedral screen.
Pixel ghosts whisper what the smiles really mean.
Everybody's talking, everybody's selling dreams,
but the truth leaks out between the broken seams.
The Oracle Buffering.
Da, da, da, da, doting, doting, da, da, da, da, doting.
Rector not.
The king says loyalty, but the queen says trust.
The user says wisdom.
Everybody's streaming from a beautiful spot.
Watch the hand.
Watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch the exits.
Watch, watch, watch, watch the play.
Marketing play.
You guys, too, if you want to.
If you didn't know, after Trix, his brother showed back up.
His brother was actually coming once in a while,
but Trix did not, he did not like outside cats,
or he does not like, or like, you know, cats that came in.
He was only used to just Rudy and Lola, Lola's his mom.
And so Trix would like start growling and I don't know,
I do have a couple cats that come visit once in a while.
They were, you know, they were raised here.
So Tux was born under the TV set.
He's really cute.
He's black.
You'll see him.
I don't know if you've seen him.
He's been here like every night for past couple weeks,
or maybe three weeks,
but he came started coming right after Trix left.
And so it kind of goes with the saying,
nothing ever really leaves.
It comes back in a different form sometimes.
But uh, yeah, he's sweet. He doesn't fight with the cats. He's not too wild
I mean, he's the one that kind of swapped like, you know
This was what it made me and scratch me
But um, it's cuz he's it was a little bit feral when he came back
But now he's gotten very sweet and he's like used to me so yeah, but he was born here
So that's really cool
You get to meet him in a minute
Hey, taxi. He's eating his food. But yeah
I'm gonna go get some of my cigars in a minute too.
Let me see.
Yeah.
He was like, but usually he would just come in at night
and then he would like, you know, be gone by morning
and stuff and then come the next night.
But this morning I woke up and then he,
he like walked out of the bedroom.
And so he's like, you know, he's moved back in,
it looks like, that's really cool.
But
Yeah, so he was born in the litter of five. He had a twin
named pie
Because they were born on pi day, which is March 14th
3.14
Right. So anyway, it's a nice day 6 11 so 6 11 minus 6 11 June 11
Family member has a birthday today a
couple of German eyes and my family German eyes are pretty interesting. They can be kind of a
A little bit of a duplicitous, well okay, all signs have the duality and like everything in the world because we live in this like dualistic
dualistic world, right, but Gemini's really are like
It's not like a good twin and evil twin. It's like kind of like two evil twins
Okay, Trump is a Gemini. He's I think on the 15th or something the 14th of the 15th
My dad was the Gemini, he was like on the 18th.
Hi, Alexandra, how are you?
I got, this is my, I don't know if you've seen Tux yet,
but he's moved back in, he was sitting next to me
and when I started, but he's eating his wet food right now,
but he's really cute.
Oh yeah, you've seen him, of course, yeah, you've seen him.
I showed you pictures, but he's gotten friendlier.
I guess it's really cool.
He's being very sweet. He comes to this next to me now and let's eat pet him.
Oh my baby. Oh my baby. No, he's just scarfing down food. But he is like, you know, he's like
in good shape. Like, you know, they just, good. Yeah, I thought I'd show him because he's here
this morning and he's like usually not here during the day. And then,
You know, I was like, I can do a show and I say, I got my window fixed. That's good.
Gemini is one of the most interesting people to talk to that soon get on your nerves.
Yeah. Okay. So yeah, Gemini's do like, so my dad was a Gemini and something he would do is like,
he would lie, he would lie, but like, it was usually for a good reason, but he would like, you know,
You try to like, you like to play the kind of pranks.
It's kind of called the divine trickster energy.
Good, divine trickster.
So what's interesting is like,
I don't like coyotes that much
because the coyote ate my cat,
but the coyote is known as the divine trickster as well.
And like, I think Native American medicine
and the coyote really resonates with
the Gemini sign.
What was interesting is the day my dad passed away,
my sister-in-law was coming down the driveway
and there was a baby coyote.
Like there was like a little baby coyote
and it's like, that's just kind of like rare, I guess, to see.
But it was kind of like one of those signs.
Like usually when someone would pass away in my family,
my grandfather, I think I saw butterflies.
My grandmother, I saw hummingbirds.
Usually it was in like the,
a couple days, and it was just like kind of like a
Weird appearance of them. And so it kind of felt like a sign to me
Like all those times and so always, you know, look out for I don't know if you guys have experienced those kind of animal omens
But it's it's pretty interesting. Hey, there's Lenore. Lenore, do you want to come over and say hi? Come on
Hi
Here she comes. Oh, there he is. He's over there. Okay. He's gonna come over to you. You hear me out
Hi Tuxi, come on. Yeah, he has a he's very vocal he has a nice meow
Yeah, he's very talkative
But yeah, all these cats get along together like you know
He's gonna use to all the oh there she is
Yeah, you're getting some camera time. Yeah
Yeah
So definitely I think so he's the one that I think that was meant
that whoever made this AI of me was meaning to like you know because he
did he kind of swatted my hand when I took the cat nymph bag like like off the
table but um yeah there is a little AI someone made it I don't think it's very
realistic though you know that's supposed to be him that's not that scene has
never happened that has never happened
I swear. Oh, oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Lenore. Oh my god. Yeah, this is what Lenore is like
just
Yeah, so my cats, you know, this is not an attack. I don't consider well. Oh come on. You know, oh
Yeah, you can tell they really she really hate me, right?
I can't I'm like the scarecrow and was it a boss. Hi, baby. Okay. You want to sit up there?
Yeah, so she's getting a little bit protective
There you go
Spanky the Norlicks little spanky
Hi tux come on
We can meet the chat when I come eat the chat. Here he comes. Oh, there he is haunt tuxi
Here is the CV there he is tux
Hi
Hi, baby
Tuxi
Happen and there we go. Hi tux
yeah, he's been like
really being sweet lately and like jumping up next to me and stuff and so
I think maybe Lenore's a little bit like that's another black cat here, but he's a little bit. He's a little bit of white on him
There he is. Hi, babe
Why?
So see he's very you know, he's very gentle now. There he is. You can see his little white. He's pretty cute. Be careful
I don't want to get another, I don't want to get another, um, you know, me made of you.
He wasn't trying to bite.
He was fine.
Okay.
But you do have to, you know, it's like, he has, I think he might be a little bit wild,
but yeah, this little tux, you see a little white, um, and he likes, likes to sit next
to me though.
That's a nice way to sit.
It's okay.
Lenore.
Oh, see, he has beautiful eyes too.
He has like these green eyes.
Hi, baby.
Can I give you a pet?
Give you a pet?
Oh, I can.
Okay, good.
Hi, babe.
Hi baby, so that's him little Tuxi. Yeah, he's like a little bit. He has a little bit of like, you know
Man I got into some some little, you know, he's been outside a lot. So I think he
Likes the outside, but I think he's like moving in
Because I just I was on this morning and I was like didn't expect to see him
Because all the cats were you know put up food for all the cats and then then he come walking out of the bedroom
So I think he he said the cats are gonna get treatment. He gets the bed here. I get the couch most of the time, right?
He took my bed
Hey taxi, we see your eyes. Talks. Can we see your eyes?
You see your eyes?
Oh, you're beautiful, huh?
He's a short hair. He's very short hair. He's born under the TV set
Hi, oh, you like to lay down you like to lay down, okay?
You can tell he's getting comfortable, right? I hope he stays happy stays, um, you know again, you know
cats do tend to like sometimes, you know wander
You know and he's used to be outside, but I hope he hope be like you know puts down his stakes here because
You know tricks, uh, I'm sure is fine
These cats are good are like little survivors, you know
Hey, right you're comfortable. See how comfortable he is. He's very comfortable. He's just chilling with me on the couch
That's Tuxi
How will this he let me see how let me think so like over two years, but two years you two years old up and
I will I do know it. I
Hi, it's very beautiful though. Look. Oh
So there you go guys you think that you know cats don't come back and
See he was gone for like a basically a year and a half, you know, I I saw him
Before my neighbors moved out. It's my neighbors really like them
They wanted to take him but he would keep her anyway. You see his little bit of white on his belly, too
You see that like right there. It's really cute. It's a little bit of white on his belly
So you're a new you're a new cat star here, you know, I
Basically, so I guess they were calling my house a feral cat colony
It's not a feral cat colony. First of all, he was born here. Oh, yep. He was born here in my house.
Okay, he was born under my TV set. He's not feral necessarily, because if he was feral, he wouldn't be
so loving and sweet and like, you know, already acclimated back into the house. So none of my
cats are feral, you know, and I mean, it's not a cat colony. It's my, my babies. And uh,
That was what was really rude about that that meme is like she posted like she's like, oh, this is
She's like my cats love me. She's like, yeah, right
She's like look at there. They're attacking because they're starving because you don't feed them and they're you know
They're and they're trying to get you know eat something and then she said
Oh, then people in the comments were like, you know, there's a person named devil lies and some other dicks
They're like, oh, um, you know, oh, well, you know, you know, oh my god, well
You know they of course they can always eat the rats outside and bring them in because he has you know
His house is covered in rat carcasses and all this kind of stuff like occasionally that might bring in a mouse
But they always take out the mouse too. They don't really like I mean Rudy used to like his um, hi, babe
Rudy's mom told me you know his his she she she gave me Rudy with like a couple like a you know
I bet a year and a half ago because she was moving and she was gonna be out of the house a lot
And so she's like can I take Rudy so I did and he was under the
under the bed for like a while.
But yeah, I don't know what was going on with that.
But anyway, Rudy's good too.
Rudy has a new place that he likes to sit.
Here you can see Rudy, hold on.
He likes to sit in the corner over here on the table.
That's your place.
I'm gonna put a cat bed over there, okay, Rudy?
I'll put a cat bed for you.
I do have plenty of cat beds.
I have a couple of cat trees.
But he just decided to,
he likes that little space over there.
They always will find their little space.
stay there right okay so I went to the library the other day and I was like
the library by me sells books right and they have like a little book cartons
Very sweet cat catnip plants. Yeah, I mean, it's a and they like catnip too
I mean, it's like there's like people are always like, oh my god
Like, you know, what's on the floor? It's sometimes this catnip because I could I put catnip everywhere
And they like to roll around in it and stuff, but yeah, so there's miss Lenore
Okay, and so, you know if you were hoping to see like oh my cats hate me
You're gonna be disappointed because they don't they love me. They really do love me
and I'm not trying to make her sell my lap or anything,
they just like, she loves me, you know, it's like,
it's true love.
So I bought this book at the library,
there was no price on it, so the lady said $2.
I think I got a good deal, so it's like
this supernatural book, and it has,
Like I think there's actually I think this is like the precursor of Batman
There's this guy that used to already read about this guy. I think what's his name?
It's like from England. I remember reading about him. His name is the the spring heel Jack
It looks like Batman to me, but it says I wish I had my glasses this
This character this crazy character was said to have
It's really small printing, it said to have terrorized Victorian England with his incredible
bounce and devilish appearance.
The first claimed sighting of the Spring Hill Jack was in 1837.
And further reports followed, thick and fast, his grotesque face, clawed hands, black cloak,
were mentioned in virtually all of the eyewitness accounts, striking fear in people's hearts.
Stories are published in the press and the precepts
were in their children, or parents were in their children, of a vast of a visit from Jumping Jack.
They misbehaved, if they misbehaved. Now...
No one fitting his unique description was ever caught some people believe that spring heel Jack was a paranormal phenomenon
But most dismiss him as a fictional story that spread into mass hysteria
That's pretty interesting. I mean, but it looks like Batman exactly and he's like, you know in Batman also
I mean, it's like he they say he looks like a devil Haitian now
So there's no nor but I but there's um, you can see talks behind me
Hi Tuxi. He's gotten comfortable. He spent the night here and he think Lenora's a little bit...
I don't think she's jealous, but you know. And was Lola when I come over here too?
Lola loves them because Lola's his mom. And Lola didn't really like care for her cat like you know
the kittens once they got to certain height. Hi Lola. You're coming over too? There's Lola. Okay.
Yeah, so there's her son and so she might go overseas, she likes to say hi to him.
That's your son, Tux?
So she's happy.
When Tux, or when Trix disappeared, she was sad.
Yeah, and Lenore's a little bit, yeah, Lenore's stoic.
Yeah, or yeah, the stole, she's like a mean stole, you mean, yeah, exactly.
Oh, yeah.
And so, and she, Lenore likes massage.
All right, they all like massage.
I'm a good cat masseuse.
I think that's why they stay here.
Okay, but you know,
I think Trix got a little horny and stuff.
He started, he was starting to like,
to like disappear for like a day or two before.
And I was like, he's gonna get lost.
I mean, I was like, but, you know, it's hard to.
You know wrangle cats, you know, they're just gonna do what they want to do
So I was just thinking like all the people that call me animal abuser for the fact that you know
one of the cats wasn't fixed or
or
What else why they why they say oh because cats please because they're outdoor cats and they have please or
Which they don't really have please you know and or what else?
Or that they're starving or something or they're not start. I mean, it's like none of those things are true
But I was just thinking like or that he ran away, you know, and it's like, oh, I was that was irresponsible of me that he ran away
Like so that'd be like calling
Literally almost every single person in the world. It's have a that's had a pet animal abuser
And I really want to know the people that say that if they've ever had a cat
Or dog disappear or pass away. I mean it's like so that's what because that's what they would say
They would say I bring they literally see I threw my cat through the window. That's why I broke they say
I ate my I eat my cats like this guy named exiled one
Me to be the AI picture of me eating the cat again a sandwich
Samann would play this thing of like me, like,
first of all, he'd be throwing tricks like a football
when he was here.
Hi, hi, babe.
And then he made like a thing of me, like,
either, I don't know if it was supposed to be,
he was supposed to be dead or something, but that,
but I was like all dirty,
like, like, like involved, like in this AI video,
like screaming for, I mean, it's like, I mean, it's so stupid.
I mean, it's like really stupid.
And it's like, you know, but, you know,
The stupidest thing with that people are saying that they're real. I mean, it's like those aren't those images. Hi
Taco cat you look taco cat. Hi. Hi. Hi beautiful. She's looking up at me with these beautiful eyes
She has beautiful green eyes. Hi, babe
So, you know, you can see I didn't like, you know, force the cat to come sit with me or anything the cats do love me
You know, so I'm not trying to like to show that I'm a good person or I'm empathetic like, you know
That's stupid a Google AI was saying, you know, it's like sometimes AI has has a
Weird theories, right? Does it know everything like I was heard. I heard AI is kind of like it's kind of like hey, P.A.G
Do you want to see talks? There's Tuxi right here
Tux Tux was born here and he's a little bit of white on him. Hi, baby
He's started to spend the night in the sub good to see you page
Hope you're doing good
But he spent the night here because you know tricks ran away. I don't know if you know tricks tricks ran away
probably a couple months ago and so tux has been back for a couple months and
He's very handsome
He has a beautiful tux. We see your white. He has a little bit of white on him. Can I pet?
He's a little bit, he's a little, maybe a little fair. No, he did not bite me, see? Yeah, the cats are cute.
Now, he has actually gotten really friendly. Hi, you just have to be like sometimes you have to be careful with how you
approach a kitty. Hi, because, you know, they, um...
I don't think he let me rub his belly yet, but I think we're getting there because he was like, you know
Laying with me like Rudy was like, you know hid for the many got here for like a month Rudy's over here in the corner
He'd like she likes to sit over there. That's his little place over there. Can you see him in the corner right there?
That's his place. And so I got all the cats around me, you know
Lenore, you're that that's Lenore. You're Miss Lenore
Hi, how are you doing?
There she is. Okay, so
Okay, Lola, I want to go to the store
So, can I get up?
See, I need to get my wallet and then I can
Have enough for a couple cigars and I think
Maybe I can get hash. What time is it? It's 10.43. So
Hmm, I can wait a few minutes and then I can get the oh shit. That's okay. Hold on. Let me see how much I have
Like I want to get maybe fries
I haven't had fries in a couple of days and I'd like to get some hot fries.
I'm sure I have enough, let me see.
Yeah, I think I do.
Okay, so I'll be good, okay?
You should be good.
I just need more matches too.
I go through matches pretty quick.
Hi, baby.
Oh, that's Miss Lola.
Lola's probably three or four and then Tux is two, you're like two and he was born March
Two years ago, so he's like two and two and almost two and a half
Yeah, but she's like a little has beautiful eyes. See she's like beautiful eyes. Oh
And they were like they're crusted over when she came you can see tux though if you came to see tuxi, there's tuxi
He's moved back in
He's really cute
he's a
Little wild but he's sweet because he was born here again
It's really interesting. I'm experienced having kittens actually
Because I've had three litters. I had a cat named Remy and Remy had two litters. And so none of like Remy nor her nor nor her
seven seven kids
Stayed here, right?
but
Lola was around when when Remy was around and Remy looked like like Lola like that. She was a little bit
little bit more thicker and she looked a little thicker and then like I think
I think Remy had like Remy had all males all the cats that were males that you
know so she had all male cats and and so then and then you could always tell
Lola was kind of wanting Lola and Lenore but Lenore's normal was fixed Lola
Before I could get her fixed right she sticks now. Oh, you're like that. She has a little cross. I like that. But yeah
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, baby. You're just cute. But yeah, when I got Lola, she had all this,
all this crust in her eyes and stuff. She's very, very sweet. She's Lola is the one that likes to
probably sleep under the covers the most. Lenore does like it, but then she gets warm and then she
like, you know, like, um, but Lola like, Hey, Brandon, what's up? What's up? How are you? Yeah.
Yeah, he's a little bit wild. You can see he's a little bit wild. I don't think so. I don't think so
I don't know if she's still here. She might have a
She might oh
Yeah, I think she I think she's she was cool
If you're still here, okay, just shout out. Okay, and so let me see I think
It's 1046 and so by the time I get the cigars I should be able to um
Go get fries too. I catch some fries and I'll walk with you guys
You can take a little walkie
And yeah, I don't know like like, you know, I have to talk to Jamie still like it was just a little little
It was like, I don't know. That's not it was a little bit weird
I just don't understand completely what happened and that will happen sometimes and it's like what happened?
because all of a sudden like
you know
Jamie and Katie like Katie was here and all of a sudden like 2020 just got timed out for like 30 seconds or something and
I didn't know because I don't really see who gets timed out
And then he's like, what happened?
And then I was like, oh, and then I don't know.
I guess there might be some bad blood or something,
but hopefully I can work it out with them.
I just, I don't know, the modding stuff,
it's like, I basically just do it just to,
so I know, like, oh, you know,
just to show appreciation.
Sometimes I don't really expect people to mod
because I can mod pretty much from my stream yard,
Okay, but yeah, okay, so let's turn on my stream yard.
Yeah, I know, I know, I love Jamie,
but I just don't know what happened.
Like, and she was like, well, and it's like, you know,
I guess, because I mod it.
I don't know, and sometimes I mod to protect people,
but you know, Jamie's a managing mod,
so she basically has like, you know, authority
to decide some stuff, but I don't know.
I don't really expect, expect modding people to mod.
Cause they're, um, okay.
So let me get on my stream yard and then I'll go for a walk.
Yeah. So I got my window fixed yesterday and guess what?
Like, so then I went in and I opened the window and,
It didn't break, but the I guess because they they they come in and they and the guy came in and you took the window
He takes it out right and he just takes out the frame and then he comes back
I mean he's gone for a while and then he can bring back the frame and stuff right that right
So that so that was fine
And then I went to like open the window and it's like as soon as I did like it started
It started splitting from the frame started splitting off the window and so I was like oh fuck
So I've already called them again and said
can they come and fix that because it's like I don't want to break it but uh okay so I'm
going to go stream yard I have another day of premium stream yard right now I'm on a trial
of course I'm stealing stream yard
I played that video last night of like the,
you supposedly stealing from the liquor store.
I'm gonna go to that liquor store right now.
If that lady's there or if that cashier's there,
I'm gonna verify that I was not stealing.
But I've been there several times since that.
Fortunately, that old lady that yelled at me wasn't there,
but she might be there today
and then I can get her to maybe apologize.
Well, she probably won't, but okay.
So let me get up, got my wallet.
We go in my pajamas. Okay. I have a bit of a jam on the bottom though. Okay, here we go. Turn off this one, follow him.
Oh my god. I can't talk. I worry my dad's broken socks going by things I inherited.
I'll show you the window I think it's open right now, but it's I mean it's fine except but I just it's split a little bit from the
You can kind of see on the
See on the side right there where it's split
Okay, it is fixed
There's the right there. There's that power plant is where they filmed
Crazy that Britney Spears song crazy. It's called. It's like this old power plant
Actually, I told Alex when I met Alex about Moonstone Beach.
Like, Redondo Beach was originally called Moonstone Beach,
and there's actually, if you go on Wikipedia, you can see.
It always says that, sorry.
There's these moonstones that would wash up on the beach.
And so it's called Moonstone Beach.
Oh, my glasses, okay.
Yeah, it's called Moonstone Beach.
And so yesterday, when I was walking home, like right here,
The neighbor was walking out with the dog well, and they're both of them the guy that like broke my window, you know and
I guess we're gonna do the thing where we pretend we don't exist
But his his girlfriend or his wife or whatever like like went across the street with the dog
Is that yeah
The moon stone each and that you laid the foundation for that with that and so there's no moon stone beach anymore
It kind of sucks
Because it was like, I guess there's a lot of good stone
or something like that that they use for the foundation.
Yeah.
So here we go.
Let me see.
Jim Jones, I look like Jim Jones with the shades. Yeah, I know I always look like a serial killer
Like well, you know, I was when I came in the community like they call me Jeffrey Dahmer
And I think some people like to like think that it's an insult but Jeffrey Dahmer wasn't a bad-looking person
I mean he's terrible terrible things and I don't want to you'd like him
But he was actually pretty good good-looking my dad actually wore glasses like this and it was so funny like we would like
One time we were here, I remember when we went to Universal Studios when I was probably like 12 or something
I was having a little brother sister around my mom and we were all like wearing white and like, you know, so happy at the theme park and it was like the sun was shining
And we were all like, all bright.
And then my dad was like in his hat and dark glasses
and like a dark coat.
And he was kind of standing like behind us.
And it looked like he was some like weirdo
like in the picture or it was so funny.
Like we were like, it looks like you're stalking us
or like, but yeah, my dad used to like have glasses
like this too, but my dad was pretty.
Pretty good looking guy. I like a lot like my dad. Actually, my dad was younger. My dad was um
He was my dad like to eat though, you know
you know, he was six too and uh
Okay, so here we go
I don't like I guess I'll go to mcdonald's first
I'm not gonna get copy there because I bought coffee. I have a copy at home now. Um, but
I cannot
We get a large fries because they're just a couple bucks
Is it as a 11 yet? Oh, five minutes. Okay, so maybe I'll get the cigars first and walk back because
So you can see there's like McDonald's is right in front of like the Catholic Church called St. James
And you can see that the cross up there. I haven't been there
I'm not Catholic. I'm like more my family's not like not Catholic
But my sister actually is now because she married Catholic guy and so they I guess they
and Bert or something, they're married in a Catholic church.
But it's interesting, communion.
And my mom was like, no, don't eat it, don't eat it.
So I don't know why it's like she didn't want me to eat it
because she's like, we're not Catholic.
So I guess it's like that you're just not allowed to
if you're not Catholic or, but, you know, I don't know.
I always wanted to eat it.
I always would try and she'd be like, no.
So hold on. Let me look at one of the McDonald's. Hold on.
Let me see. Okay. Let me. Okay. So, okay. So also, so it's a redondo beach.
Like I said, there's a library right there and see it says Civic Center and there's like a big tower.
Look at that. What is that tower? That is like a, that is like a big, massive, scary ass tower.
Like, I don't even know what that is for. Like, what is that for? Is that for like, is his mom, you know?
You know, she had a police scanner and she was like listening all the time to the police scanner and you know
And she could hear him when he was on duty and stuff. Now redondo is not a very dangerous city
But it is next to kind of some dangerous cities and there's maybe like a more dangerous part of it
But um he was actually shot on duty one time and I think he was wearing a bulletproof vest and
Stuff and so he was fine. My grandma is actually listening to the police scanner when he got shot
But any time I've ever had any kind of legal trouble. Oh, it smells like fries already
It's the hash browns or fries. You haven't ever had like a little just I just had minor minor minor things
But um, you have anything happen like, you know, you just mentioned I got pulled over for traffic ticket
You just mentioned my uncle was the sergeant and sometimes it works. Sometimes so let's see. So this is also a nice McDonald's actually
There's nobody in it right now
Is it 12 yet? Okay. It's a
Two minutes I'll just walk back. I'll walk to the liquor store first
My two impatient right now. So there's the Starbucks over there. There's redonna, you know high school
The redonna unions interesting because Tracy lords went to the redonna union
Tracy lords with a porn star
that's very well known because she like used the fake ID to get into porn and
Because of that like all her porn had to be recalled
Really because they were called like, you know underage porn or whatever. I think she was 16 or 17. She went to that high school
so
Yeah, I mean, it's like I'm sure that there were some
And is anybody I mean, I think who goes there. I think just one of my I think may know I think all my all my nephews
Store in this corner called
That's gone. It had some full stuff, but it's not the best place or
Or a store because it's kind of like in this presidential little area
Okay, so I'm gonna walk to the corner store. I did not shoplift the Swisher
Okay, first of all, I had to ask for the Swisher
Second I said second of all I had to like, you know my car through the cashier was new
I'm gonna explain this again cashier was new and so she didn't understand how it quite worked
But I could I heard it beep and I saw I was like did I don't think it went through and I told her that
She goes, no, I went through and I was like, really?
Okay, so I just took her word for it.
I walk out and then like the owner who like lives
in one of these apartments with her husband,
her husband's wife, and she's like Korean stealing.
I was like, I wasn't stealing.
And then she's like, how are you, wife?
And I was like, you're yelling at me, lady.
And she's like, oh, you, I don't know.
She didn't do it.
I didn't even care about doing my Korean impression.
Too close to them.
Thank you, but right down here is the ocean and the okay, so okay, I need to you don't okay, so I think
Okay, figure it out. So here we go
Okay
Hi, how are you? Can I get to a switcher, please any of you?
Thank you, can I get matches, please? Thank you so much
or let's ask for the, okay, there we go.
Okay, now back to McDonald's.
Now it is time for the fries.
So I can, I actually like,
I don't need to order from the app.
You know, it's better.
Okay, so if you have the McDonald's app and stuff,
like it, like, oh, it only lets you like,
order like one of the deals at a time.
I'm only ordering one anyway,
but did you have the fries still on sale?
They had coffee for a dollar for a long time.
You even had ice coffee for a dollar.
But I think that now it's like $4 and so that's why I buy my own coffee now, but
But yeah, but they also have do you have free refills and it's like I think if you buy it in the morning
You should be able to like you don't come back like they never gave me a problem
I never had I've never been refused a refill you have to ask them for it. It's not like though. It's like it's not that again
It's not like stealing. I mean, it's like people like to twist the shit around so much
To make me seem like I'm some kind of piece of trash person. It's okay. You're fine. Okay
Guy almost hit me with this truck.
Okay, so is it 11 yet?
Yes, it is.
Okay, now I can get the prize.
I think they start serving lunch at McDonald's at 11.
I just feel like a nice hop down for a second.
I'll be right back.
I think I need to get in here before the, before it's lunch.
I'll see this, all these teenagers are walking over now.
So hold on, let's see.
Oh, I'll be right back with you in a second.
I don't, I never steal anything.
Yeah.
Okay, so here's the DL, folks.
Any size, except the basket.
You can't get a basket of fries, of course, but $2 fries.
Maybe next time to go out today.
Okay, $2.18.
Okay, let's hope I have it.
Okay, pay right here and see if I have any luck.
Okay.
Never mind
I guess I spent it all on see. I'm not I'm not a thief, but occasionally I am poor
Especially
Okay, you know secret cigars are great appetite. Oh
Well, I should have like search for more change my Christians. I always find
You know, yeah, I didn't get the dot dot dot dot dot feeling today. I got that that declined
But see if I would have gotten the prize before,
then I would have gotten,
I might have gotten declined at the store.
And then that would be embarrassed, more embarrassing.
I don't know, I'm not willing to,
I'm not afraid to like embarrass myself.
You guys probably know.
But the only thing that bothers me is when people like
exaggerate or lie, they're playing out lie,
which is what they tend to do.
I think my life is embarrassing enough alone on its own without without me having to like, you know, you put into like AI
Pictures and then and then at the same time
Criticized for me using AI, but then not only are they using it. I mean they're using it. It's just ridiculous. Yeah, well, I'll give you
to my art
but I'll say she is creative because how in the fuck did you go from what she looks like into
what her profile picture looks like? I mean that is quite an imagination right there.
I mean so if you've got to hand it to her maybe I don't have an imagination and she does, right?
But people think that I'm like some kind of idiot or something like I don't know how to write
or like maybe like I don't even know how to read. I actually like I learned how to read when I was
I thought it was really good English. I was an honors English. I actually graduated from college.
And so, you know, all this stuff, like, I'm so dumb, I can't even like, you know, write a song
or anything like that. It's kind of like, you know, a little bit insulting, but he didn't,
he never fixed it or he or it's pregnant or something. And he, and he lives in his like
truck, but he's, I don't, I don't hear him getting criticized or, you know, any of that.
I don't know.
Like God loves you everybody.
Anyhow, I'm on my street, it's pretty street.
Maybe I'll find something change and I'll go back later
and get some or something, I don't know.
It's like, I'm not even gonna,
I'm trying to bother, like anytime I even try,
I mean, I'll do my like clapping, but it's like,
I'm just like so sick of like being called grifter
and like, it's like, or like, you know, asking for anything.
It's like, it's like, I'm just like,
So I've been so slandered and attacked and like, you know, made to look like such a people
Like I don't know. I don't I don't know if there's a there's a person I've seen on YouTube that has been like
Like accused of like, you know being such a like a horrible person than myself like I mean, I mean
I don't even see people really good
I mean you have some people get criticized especially for people that don't like them, but it's just like for me
It's like it's like I just bring out the
The side of people that where it's like it's just like they just hate me
That's okay. I don't mind being like the most hated person even though. I didn't like really do anything to be hated for
I mean, let's do it. I'm a Capricorn. We are the devil. Oh
I'll just play the devil
You know
Worst, you know, the worst it seems to get so I don't know I even try
That's what I want. It's like, you know
Okay, my phone might go up for a second because I'm feeling back at my property so
One second. Oh, I'll see you in a second. I'll be right, I'll be right there.
Kind of, I mean, he's my, oh, he's my, he's my cat. Um, Bucks, um, I've had, he was born here and stuff.
He's been gone for like a year and a, like over, like about a year and a half,
but he's in the bedroom right now. He's taking a nap.
But yeah, he's kind of moved back in and he came right up for tricks, but he's now he's really assimilated to the person
That said oh, you came in before a small fry. My father must be really disappointed in me. I just want to address that person
First of all was a large fry
Okay, and second of all
Are you are you supporting me? Is that in your business third of all?
Yeah, my father is proud of me because you know, I'm not in prison. I'm not dead
And I'm doing what I want to do following my dreams, but you know what?
I'm sure your parents are really proud of you being just a troll on YouTube.
And that's all you are and that's all you'll ever be.
I didn't lose them. He was, you know, he kind of ran away.
Yeah. Oh, after Tricks ran away? Yeah. After Tricks, you know, after Tricks got lost.
Yeah, he came back. Well, he would kind of like, more recently, he was like,
wouldn't Tricks with us here? He would come in and then Tricks would just like, you know,
like, hiss and like, attack him and stuff.
Yeah, I'm sure they are. I mean it's like, I mean people are ridiculous. My father has passed away
It's his birthday coming up and just to just to bring him up at the site is sick the sickest thing
It's like he was way too good for to be in that person's mouth
I mean, it's like so don't even reference or you know, I'm too good for that person. I mean, it's like
so they're gone
it's probably
That big, you know lard, but Kate or something like that. I bet anyway
Yeah
Yeah, well, it's like, you know, I told my dad I wanted to do YouTube and he's like, you should do it, you know, do it.
And I did. And so, you know, it has its ups and downs and stuff, but it's, uh, you know, I'm still here.
Yeah, so it's his birthday. His birthday is right around Father's Day, so we always celebrate it like at the same time.
And, uh, so I'll be celebrating his birthday soon.
Yeah, this is my father.
He like, um
He really loved me like really loved me and you know
Yeah, oh, yeah, he was even I mean it's like even if I you know if I didn't do it
He would have a huge you know, he always was you know, he always said he was proud of me or whatever, but um, you know
I always like you know, he was such a
like a
like a very successful like wonderful person like you know, I can't ever like a
like probably reached his level, you know, but
No, I'm proud of him. So anyway, I mean, but it's like really, I just wish like I wish that upon them
I mean, I wish that they the people get to feel like what they they dish out. I really do. I really do. I
Think they do. I think that's part of like the part of life is like
feeling everything especially what you do to others. I think it always comes back to you and
Yeah, so I just like harm you take care of it. There's just a little more
Have a little nap on my lap?
Nap on my lap?
Yeah, he was very good.
I can read you some of his obituary, but I mean it's like
then people might try to Google and I don't know.
I think Q or something was putting his picture up or something.
Around the time, you know, his anniversary of his death,
but whatever, but I can tell you like he
he was you know very smart he was like he was like you know kind of like an
amateur architect he designed he was in charge of this whole redesign of his
beach club by our house he loved
He loved, well, see how I gave that like little tour?
Like he was like the best tour guide.
He could, he could go to Hollywood or Glendale.
Like he grew up in Glendale,
but he could give a tour of anywhere
and like in Palm Springs or anywhere.
And he was so good at like,
he just knew every like little story,
every celebrity had lived and he would just drive around.
He loved cars.
He loved like, you know, the Cowboys and,
and you know, old PBS.
Black and white movies and he loved wine. He loved good dinners. He loved my mom
He loved all his kids, you know, he had
You know, but there's seven of us and so, you know, but he himself had five and my mom had
Five but together but together they had three so there's seven to get it all together
Yeah, he was I mean he was really he was really very very creative and like he wasn't an architect
But he would but they the pit if he would like always be when he was basically a contractor and like you know did a lot
of a like real estate and so he would like draw blueprints and stuff and
You know, it's just like, you know, it's really
difficult. He would also take me to lunch every week. We would go into this place called
Joe's, which is like, he was like, he did Joe's. And there's a couple of John Wayne
omelet and he always had his big omelet. And I would have like a tuna melt. And even
like, he was always like, even when he got sick, he was like, he wanted to like still,
he's like, Oh, when I get better, we'll come take you out. And like, but he never got better.
But, you know,
Then once he got sick he was ready to go to and he went really quickly once he once the doctors had said like you know
It's pretty much. It's over like he was ready to go and like we try to keep him like alive
If you don't want to take his medicine or shit like that
So please take your medicine, but I mean I well I kind of knew he wanted to go
So I was like, you know, I was in support of whatever he wanted to do, but
But like, you know, thankfully he didn't suffer for too long, but, you know, and he did hide he did not tell, you know
us until like kind of like
We didn't know like he was sick until well, I mean for my mom did and he knew but he kept it very quiet up until
Yeah, he had he got bladder cancer and it was it had spread by the time into his like lymph nodes by the time
He got diagnosed and stuff and so it was not sick. It was not a comfortable
Kind of thing to have, you know, and then he he was like when he was in his bed
he just hated that I mean he just did not like to be in bed and
Because he was like always wanting to move he was 80s
He was at 86 and he was still going to work every week, you know and and working and stuff is you know, and so
I don't know this. I just wanted to share a little bit about him, but you know he
He's a great guy like his father was my grandfather. I never got to meet my grandfather on his side
But he was a salesman. Oh your mom's a cancer nurse. Yeah
Like we like we well he was under like I forgot what it's called
But it's like it was kind of like hospice care. It's like the end of life thing
where they where he was like, but it did it at home, you know and
and so he would have these Filipino nurses come and
And you really like the Filipino nurses. He said they had like the best attitude
like they're always friendly and he's like even like I think one time he told a story like he
knocked over when he woke up in the middle of the night or something in the hospital when he's
in the hospital and he uh he knocked over this like this like thing of blood or something that was
on his on his on his desk stand this like this and it like broke all over the floor and he said
like the nurses came in and we're just singing mopping it up and stuff and uh and even like there
some gay nurses and stuff like that but he was always like you know he was always like
he was not he was always very accepting of me and stuff and so he liked everybody and you know
but uh yeah so he's the reason I mean if you probably mean it's like yeah he took really good
care um yeah had you know yeah you are intuitive
That was very intuitive. Yeah, I mean it's like but um, yeah, that's basically like I think heart disease and cancer are like some of the big killers of
People but it's like, you know eventually if you live long enough, you're probably gonna get one of those
You know, it's like and 86 years old is he like he didn't have a bucket list
He was like do you have a boyfriend or partner? No, I do not I like I I'd never even really dated very much
I dated like a woman once
for like a few months in like 2012 or something like that when I was 33 and that was kind of
traumatic and I haven't like since then I've I've been like really looking for it's hard for like
I think it's hard for like men to like be with other men because men are like I don't know unless
they have open relationships I just think it'd be kind of hard for like a minute like again
I, yeah, I am, no, I am, but I did just happen to date a woman, I guess I was experimenting
in my 30s or something, it's quite an experiment, it's kind of one of those experiments that
kind of blows up in your face, but yeah, she was a witch, at least she had a magic spell
on me or something, so whatever the Persian spell is, nothing compared to what I experienced.
This is good.
Good stuff.
Vanilla latte.
That's good stuff.
Check out the business card.
It's for a gift.
Got business cards from a great friend.
I'm going to thank them because they're beautiful.
And I don't know, maybe I'll do some, you know, if anyone wants one in the future, just let
me know.
We can autograph one or something.
With one of those metal pens. Hi, Lenore. So there's Lenore. Oh, you're just comfortable. I
Hi
Yeah, so um, also, I do I do like you did a minute and you're lesbian. Okay. Wow. Oh your woman
Okay, and you have a girlfriend your relationship with guys was abusive. Okay. You're a lesbian
Okay
And you feel like it was because I feel like women are like kind of naturally for the most part by sexual
There's exceptions, of course
Like you know the very highly heterosexual women that are just and I kind of like you know
They're strictly dickly I guess they say but then there's I think there's women that are like
You know that could go either way and I think that sometimes this is this is Lenore right here
This is Lenore tuxes in the bedroom, but I'm tuxes a little bit of white on his chest. Lenore's the girl and
Tucks a little bit more wild. He is and he has his green eyes. Your eyes are beautiful. They're beautiful yellow eyes
It's beautiful. She's beautiful eyes
But he's really cool
But he's now he's he was he never was here during the day
So when he came out this morning of the bedroom, I was like, oh my gosh, he spent the night
Okay, so they weren't really romantic. Yeah, I don't think it's hard. It's kind of like hard to deal with men
I think like for the most part like women would like
you know, if they, if they had a choice, sometimes they would like, you know, prefer to like be raising children with just other women, like, like, I think, like, you know, men can be very dangerous, occasionally, and like, you know, also, like, you know, overbearing, like, especially, like, you know, when you're single at a certain age, like, you guys know that guy, J1, I know, like, J1, and maybe, like, you know, and I love Mason, but, you know, I did hear, like, you know, those guys, like, they like to.
Like and I'm like not gonna criticize because I also will friend like people like a lot of people because I'm like a
Networker and a marketer and stuff and I'd like to like, you know
And so I look I will like, you know friend every suggestion on Instagram
And I'll like kind of follow everybody on Twitter that I can't and I'll do it every day
I'll you know, so I'll follow a lot of people and so sometimes there's people like you know blogger
I guess is like why is he trying to follow me is it on Instagram is he like he trying to
I was like, no, it's just because I don't even look at the names.
I just go accept, accept, or I just go add friend, add friend to the suggestions or whatever.
You've only had feelings for women?
Yeah.
Well, yeah, it's like I mean it's like I mean I had like kind of like romantic feelings for the woman
But I mean or I have like romantic feelings, but I don't have a sexual feeling. I guess it's weird
But um and then it's like but then it's like men are like really difficult to deal with and it's like and I'm not like
But then again, I'm a romantic and so I'm not like into like just having sex and so I've basically been celibate for quite a while
And not really trying. I mean it's like but um
Wow, Bita was bringing up like last year.
I mean, I did have a show where I was like,
we're on Grindr and stuff.
And like, you know, Bita was like,
no, don't like, I think she had a crush on me at the time.
So she was like telling me and she said no to everybody.
Like, she's like, no, don't, I was like,
this guy's cute.
She's like, no, no, no.
And then it didn't work.
It didn't quite work out with the guy I met.
I met and so I was like, I'm not ever gonna date again.
And I don't like, I'm not really into like the,
the promiscuous lifestyle.
I'm actually kind of old fashioned and boring.
Boring, I don't even really like sex.
I mean, it's like, I'm more into like,
like I said, cuddling and stuff.
I'm like more like, I find sex is like
a little bit extreme to me.
And it's, well, also boring.
I don't know, it's like, it's weird, it's weird.
So guys, are you anybody, I'm gonna give you like,
if anyone's interested in a,
Like like working with like the kind of AI I work with like and I'm probably probably heard of you know
You probably know about you know, you know, of course everyone knows chat CPT and then it's like that less people are aware of Claude
But um the same time
I don't know if you know how like how amazing it is and so I do have like I think I can have a few memberships I can or like
Few other things I can give give away. Hold on. Let me see my settings
Three things to give away or something like that. I can try but they did that with Claude right now. There's a new a new
It's like the new brain of it like that. They always always called their called models. So there's one called
It was called mythos or MIT HOS, but it was so powerful that and because it was like it could like it's capable of like
Hacking and doing all these high-security things and like so they
They only released it to like certain companies, right?
Some certain companies.
And then, but they did eventually release it,
but they modified it.
They released it under a name called Fable.
Fable is basically basically they does everything and the mythos does it's basically mythos
But then it's like for certain things they have a safety net
So certain things it will it will take it down and have the other models figure out like security things and like certain like you know
controversial things
Let me see if I have a I do have a link if anyone wants to
Let me see what it says hold on
I can find it.
Okay, so there's something called Claude code,
and that's what I did use for my website.
And so here, and if you do like it and try it
and everything, you know, this is like a referral.
So hey, charisma, how are you?
Hope you're okay too, good to see you.
Yeah, so.
there. If you want to check that out, there's my referral link for it. I would get like
some credit, like a little credit if you were to sign up. But I will also like, I'll like,
if you don't want one, so I'll do, if you sign up, I'll do like a tutorial for you and
give you some really good advice because it's really amazing. But yeah, they're offering,
like they let you use the Fable model, I guess until the 22nd or something like that. You can
you know for I don't know if it's for the pro members or but I don't know it's really really
powerful I was able to do a lot of stuff I mean I would have had this there's so much
I mean I see I'm a really late starter because I'm 45 years old whatever but it's like I was always
I mean I've done websites before but it's like you know I'm not I wasn't like that good at coding
Because coding is really complicated and it's like if you get like I'm not very detail-oriented, you know
And I like to do things fast. I'm a bit more of an ideas person
And so that's what's really great about like, you know either AI and also the vibe coding that's people are doing now is
that it's really
It's really bad ideas and then basically you can give the ideas others Rudy
You give the idea and then it's like, you know, and then you can just work along with it and and you know
clarify the idea make it better and and come out with so that's how I did my
website you have a lot of feelings yeah I mean I have a lot of feelings too I'm
I think I have like a woman a woman's brain basically
And it's not like, but it's not like, I feel like a woman.
It's basically I have a woman's brain.
It's like, well, it's like maybe,
maybe we're more like, no, you don't.
I, maybe I don't know what it's like,
but I just think in the sense that I'm like very receptive.
I'm very, you know, I have empathetic, empathic.
see women have a lot of feelings but that's the thing it's like women feel
more but they're not like and their people will say oh women are so emotional
but they're actually men are more men are emotional but and women are women are
more they feel it I think they feel things stronger like they like they feel
like they smell sharper they see sharper like and then they they feel more
And men are kind of like, and I, oh, there's Lola.
Men are kind of like discouraged to have,
to express their feelings by other men sometimes,
or sometimes by women, or they're made to feel bad,
you know, if they, like,
but the women do like men to show feelings,
but it's like at the appropriate times, I think.
But women are like the more emotional ninjas.
They're more like, so it's like,
that's why they feel more big in this one,
but they're better.
I think they're better at understanding emotions.
There's more experts at it.
And men are like emotional babies kind of,
and then women are kind of like the emotional ninjas.
So they can kind of like have a one-up on men on that
because they can kind of, you know,
they want you, they can manipulate them.
It's not sometimes they do, but, you know,
but I did notice that like women do like men
who can, a man that can cry, but at the right,
it's the appropriate time.
Like a man with a heart, but not like,
I'm not a man that's like so sensitive. He cries at everything, right? It's like that's like a turn off
but it's like a man that can cry at the right time or
So they at least know he has emotions because a lot of men can seem like very psychopathic or cold or something like that
Hi, Rudy
I don't know, maybe I just have a lot of theories about things.
That's Rudy.
Hi.
Yeah.
So Tux is still here, but he's just inside the bedroom and he's moved into my bedroom.
See, she thinks I'd die with cats.
My cats get the bed.
I'll take the couch, right?
So yeah, so, yeah, but oh yeah, so, but with the Mithos model anyway, it's called Fable.
It's really good, but it goes really fast because you get a certain amount of usage of it,
and then it resets over a few hours, and then you get a weekly usage. I'm almost done with
my weekly usage, and it's only a couple days into the week for the model, and I go through it.
Yeah, thank you so much. Yeah, especially right now. I do appreciate if you press the like,
because there is a campaign to come to my page. Just call me a predator protector and then
Oh yeah, make sure you leave a dislike.
That's what they say.
So anyway, and especially because this is a backup channel,
it does like, I didn't notice that there were very few likes
from my streams lately.
And then there's like a lot of dislikes.
And so it's like people are more motivated by hate
than I guess love, which is a sad thing.
But if you can be motivated by love for a second
and helping me out,
because it does help probably help the algorithm
and help me get recommended a little bit more.
So I think that, hey, butterfly.
So that's one of the reasons I think that, yeah.
So if anyone wants a reading I'll do free readings today or if you want to upgrade it one or whatever
Just let me know
Or I'll do in general. I have I like so much stuff. I like hundreds of books
I there's some there's so few things that I've actually brought out of my bedroom and stuff like that to share with you
I mean, I was like, you know, I've had like a lot of the same stuff for even for like the past year and a half
I have like a lot of decks to give a certain deck. You'd like a reading. Okay?
Do you want, do you want, I have like a couple decks, I have a couple of Disney decks, I don't know,
some people think you don't think it's dumb, but I think they're really good decks. There's an
Alice in Wonderland deck and the villains, Disney villains, and they're right over there.
If you would like one of those, or I have, what else do I have? I have a, I'm looking right here,
I have one called the Magical deck, which has like kind of like little stuff in it, and then I have
like the kind of scary decks on my table right now. I've also have Ganesha deck, so just let me
I'll start out with some, I'll start out with some oracles, oracles for you, these are just
short oracles and then I'll, I'll do like, I'll do like a couple from each of these for you and
then I'll, you want a magical one? Okay.
So I'll start with this fairy. This fairy says believe and it says magic is there when you believe
So dream big things you can't achieve and this is like really believing in yourself and something
Maybe you like not even lacking confidence in something
But it's like there's just remember all things are possible if you believe in yourself
And it's like the only person to tell you you can't do something is you know you really it's like no one else can tell you
This one also says sleep. I don't know if you've been
Having problems with sleep lately, but it says underneath the site
I don't need to do the nighttime skies, fairies, singing you lullabies and so maybe this will
help you sleep, okay?
Or maybe you need to get some more sleep or, and that will be helpful for you.
Okay, a couple from this one, this is the, this is called the secret garden.
This one says wildflower, live in uncontrolled life, free to grow anywhere and bound by nothing.
Okay, you've been sleeping good? Okay. Well, maybe the fairies have been helping you out. So there's wildflowers, okay?
Or you're a wildflower, you know
And then we have share it says the busy beach. It's still make time for every flower
So, you know share as you have something to share with the world, I think and you know
It's art music or even just like, you know, your your likes dislikes, you know share with people also
We have recharge. There's nothing like a walk on the beach to
Soothe your soul, okay, you can recharge.
And there is a voyage, set sail on a new course.
And so maybe some kind of new, you're an artist, awesome.
Yeah, so share your art.
And then it's like, and then it says recharge.
And that's another thing to do with like,
just make sure you're getting enough rest
and it's good you're sleeping.
And then voyage, maybe either a trip
or it's like, there's some kind of new direction
you wanna go in life and have the confidence
and believe in yourself that you can do it.
I'll grab the magic deck.
Okay, be right back.
Okay.
So this is kind of a different deck.
This is called Magical Spell Cards.
And so it is by Lucy Cavendish,
which is a really cool name.
And okay, it's a sacred keys to effective casting
and crafting, okay.
They're beautiful cards with the back of the card, okay.
Kind of like lifting the veil a little bit.
Okay, so let me see.
Okay, I have not used these very much.
Thanks for suggesting this deck.
Okay.
Okay, what do we have? Okay, this one says best possible decision. It says Artemis the goddess of
The bow help me see what must be known. Okay, so there's like something some kind of decision, okay?
and I think this is a sign that you're making
the best possible one.
Maybe something you decided that was a hard decision
or something like that,
but it's like she has helped you with that
and I'll read you from the book about it
because this is a unique deck
and so I want to read from the book
and I'll pull you through from this deck, okay?
So it says best possible decision.
Sometimes in life we must,
or art we,
We souls in human form are presented with a path that does not simply fork but branches
off in many different directions, where nothing seems clear and each route has its wonders
and its woes.
Decisions may seem valid in the moment and even imperative to make, yet we need to ask
This is truly when this spell is helped straight from the universe to you.
Via the magic of this spell, the universe will offer you guidance, even show you what
decision would be best for you to make under current circumstances.
Do not seek to know the ultimate outcome.
The ways of the universe are mysterious.
and the very best lessons along the way.
If this card, this spell card magically chose you,
you will soon have divine aid
regarding the important decision you're about to make.
Take a deep breath and work with magic.
You are being given this energetic solution in life's muddles.
Unclear thoughts and this sea sawing of your mind.
Soon you will be clear, direct, and like an arrow from the bow of the goddess Artemis,
straight and true.
If you chose the spell, you already know there is a new road to walk or chance to take.
But there are several options for you.
What will the answer be?
If you're afraid of making a decision because you are afraid of making a mistake, the spell
will help to give you the results to take action. Be heartened by the guidance the
spell will offer you and go slowly on your new path. Great change can truly make
take place in the pauses between each breath.
When we act with clarity and true direction,
this spell will offer you all of this and much more.
So this is called the best possible decision spell.
It says cast a spell at a new or a crescent moon.
You will need a candle, jasmine oil or moonstone
or pearl and a quartz crystal.
Go to your sacred space,
see a beautiful ring of silver shining
energy circling all about you. This is the pure, adventurous, and fierce energy of Artemis,
a goddess of great clarity and precision. She will help you to hitch your mark.
Carve the crescent moon into your candle to represent
The bow of Artemis, anoint your candle with jasmine oil, blend with a little base oil,
so it is gentle in your hands and light your candle. Hold the moon stone in your left hand,
and the quartz crystal in your right hand. Hold up your left hand and chant three times.
Artemis, goddess of the bow, help me see what must be known.
Keep me straight, on track and true, help me decide, help me choose.
Aid me now to find any way by silvered night, by golden day.
Help me make the choice that's right. I ask you now lend me your might Artemis bright goddess
I thank thee and by the power of three times three as I do will so motion be okay
You recently gave your girlfriend a promise ring. Wow, that's awesome
So feel the energy moving in your left hand and imagine yourself holding a great silver
bow.
Feel the energy shifting and transferring to your right hand and imagine you are reaching
back drawing an arrow from a quiver, placing it in the notch with the bow and tightly drawing
up the string of the bow.
Launch your arrow of energy high into the universe and be guided by Artemis to the right decision.
Feel the arrow launch and let it go.
Thank Artemis again for the gift of clarity and blow out your candle, sending the energy forth on a wish.
See the silver circle shining bright and being reabsorbed into the universe.
That night, sleep with the moon stone and clear quartz beneath your pillow.
Before the moon reaches her fullness, you will have made the right decision.
And so if you want a little bit more help or if you have another decision to make,
that might be a good guidance. And so make sure you save this episode so you can
go back and listen to that. Okay, so let's do another one. We have justice. Okay.
And here we go again, by the power of three times three, maat, deliver justice to me. Okay.
We have the scales which is a kind of a Libran energy. Okay, and this is card number five. Okay
They're beautiful cards
Okay, so the justice says
All of us and all our lives experience times when we feel disempowered and taken advantage of.
When we feel we have been treated unfairly or with a lack of justice,
it is only natural to wish to restore fairness to a situation and to bring a better resolution for ourselves.
One which recognizes our natural right to respect, to fairness, and to being seen and heard as equals.
This is what we yearn for justice.
If this card has chosen you, please respond with wisdom to the magical message and to
the action it suggests you take.
The universe is acknowledging that justice must be done, will be done, and that you deserve
more than you may be receiving at the moment.
Being chosen by this card reminds you to trust the laws of cause and effect which are always
at play within the universe.
It also reminds us of the law of the threefold return, mentioned in the introduction of this
guidebook.
When we send out, we'll return to us by the power of three.
So clear yourself of vengeful feelings
and be clear and calm when you cast.
This is about justice, not vengeance.
The spell is powerful and can bring about a positive outcome
in a fair and balanced way.
When we cast this spell and work with this magic,
the wheel turns and this time in our favor,
in the direction which most benefits us.
If you have chosen the card,
strongly requested to clear yourself of feelings and vengeance and hatred and to
come to a place of good intentions for yourself and justice that will reach.
Change and educate others. The spell is not a plaything for gaining advantage but
a magical series of actions which will draw change to a situation where there
has been an imbalance.
and injustice. Well done on taking actions and being clear, brave, and true when you do this.
Change is coming.
So this spell can be worked at any part of a moon cycle.
You will need a piece of blue or white cloth about 15 centimeters or six inches in diameter,
quartz crystal any size, four gold coins, several grains of black pepper,
sea salt, a little earth, and a golden thread. Charge all of these items you need for the
spell work on your altar for about an hour. Go to your altar and visualize a circle of
blue light surrounding you. Take your cloth and place the crystal, the coins, the black pepper,
and the earth in the center gather the cloth up so it forms a little pouch and take the golden
thread and wind it three times closing the patch
Securely, while doing this chant by the power of three times three, ma'at deliver justice
to me.
As themus wills, make it so that the power of justice flow, visualize justice coming
your way.
Imagine how good this will be, how you will benefit and how this will be a valuable experience
for all concerned.
Reflect also on what you have learned and what you can do with the wisdom.
truly feel this, let the blue circle of energy about you transmute and be reabsorbed into the
universal energies all about you. Thank ma'at, the Egyptian goddess of justice, and Themas,
the Greek goddess of justice, to spend the pouch in a place that is significant to you.
Over work papers, near the telephone, or anywhere where it would be best to do work,
justice will wheel about and be ever in your favor. Okay, and we have one more for you.
It's because it's like, no, I appreciate you being here.
Okay, finally we have health.
And there's a health card, okay, health.
And it says, mother earth, sweet, mother earth bright,
bring me your health and might, okay?
So there's some, this is for good health, okay?
And she's reaching above and below.
The guy's above, still below, okay?
We're kind of these intermediaries between the earth
and the sky, so that's number 30.
Okay, so it says, health is always desirable.
And when we have experienced the glow of true health,
we have just experienced it
as a natural sense state of being.
It is the absence that most often teaches us what health is.
The spell will help to bring good health to yourself.
And if someone you care for is ill,
it may be a benefit to cast this on every half.
If you were chosen by the spell,
you're being reminded that you can help
yourself or a person you feel concerned for. Please put any fear you feel aside and cast for
yourself on behalf or on the other person. It is always best to seek their consent first. However,
if this is not possible, you may simply work with energetic magic on their behalf asking for
the highest good for all concerned. If you chose a spell for yourself, you may also know that help
vitality that magic will bring. The universe loves you and wishes to support you. So allow
it to bring healthy energy to you and those you care about through this beautiful spell.
So it's a short spell. It says cast a spell on a Sunday or anytime during a waning moon.
You will need a blue candle. A neutral color is fine if you're using a beeswax or a soy candle
and three drops of raven
uh, raven-serra oil, uh, make a lovely healing so-soup of organic vegetables and stock.
Go to your altar and see wing-circle of white light all about you.
See the white light flowing all around you moving through you and clearing any areas
where potential ill health is residing.
Noist your candle with the oil, being careful not to touch the wick.
Light your candle and chant three times.
Mother earth, sweet mother earth bright.
Bring to me your healing might, mother earth strong, pure and bright, encircle me with healthy light.
Make me well, let me shine, truly my body is divine, and by the power of three times three,
as I do will, so mode it be. Blow out the candle, then head outside and lie down upon the earth.
Let your palms and feet really feel the earth. Let all that is unwell flow from your body
into the earth to be transmuted. When you feel this energy has truly flowed
free from you into the earth, take a moment to breathe deeply in and out three times. Move to a
new space, lie down again and with the next in breath feel the deep healing energy of the sacred
earth blow on to you. Feel yourself full of this wonderful energy and feel your own energy shift
change and rework so you become healthy, strong and full of vitality and life force. Return to
Softer as is reabsorbed into the energy of the universe and no health is now yours blessed be so there you go
Hope you like those all awesome
Yeah, so there's a few people here. I mean, it's like if oh, I mean guys
I mean you can like let me see I'm gonna say to the lurkers if there's workers. You're welcome no problem
Yeah, I have the lurk spell, but if you want to un-lurk, you just have to go un-lurk, but I'm putting the lurk spell on the lurkers, and so lurkers
Well, you're glad you liked it. Glad you liked it
Yeah, but thank you. I love doing readings and so, you know, I'm gonna do a lot more free readings and stuff
So my ancient decree all lurkers must present themselves before the High Council of bad decisions. Okay, you have to go un-lurk
or else you have to go to the council bad decisions, okay, everybody? Okay, um, so yeah,
yeah, I've been doing terrorists since I was about eight years old, and it's like people will be like,
oh, yes, I did. And it's like, maybe I wasn't very good at it until probably my,
I'm probably as a teenager, I got pretty good at it, but I would say I'm really good at it now.
I also did like, over a thousand readings on Etsy, paid readings and stuff.
But, uh, that was during the pandemic when there's a lot more, um, interest in life in that, um, you know, because now you can just go on YouTube and stuff.
And I'm a lot of free readings, but my sister used to go ice skating and, um, and so I would be bored and my mom was like, okay, go buy something for the bookstore, pick something from the bookstore.
So I picked tarot cards and I had a couple decks went up before I was ten years old
I didn't have a couple of decks some people are like now you get it. Yeah, it's just like what people always
Be contrary to what I say, right?
Let me know your sign though. Oh, what's your sign?
Because I can probably give you some interesting information if anyone wants to have the question I might do horoscopes today
I have some prepared actually.
So just think a minute, I can read everyone's sign
because I'm just in the mood to do this right now.
Okay, let me just grab this up.
Okay, okay.
Okay, this is kind of like there's like twin soul themes.
Okay, so we're gonna start with the sign of Aries.
Aries is the baby of the zodiac, of course.
Okay, and so this is a mystical horoscope.
Um, for, and I call this a twin soul horoscope because of Gemini and that's, you know, Gemini is almost like a two that you're twin soul.
And it's, uh, so for divine counterparts, and, uh, then the pay, I'll give you your patron, your patron deity for your sign.
And this will guide you through the rest of June.
And so for Aries, June will bring you.
Your patron, of course, Aries is the god Aries.
He is the god of war, because Aries is ruled by Mars.
Aries is the red planet, Mars is the red planet,
has to do with war and energy and things like that.
But Jun will bring you a test of patience.
So your twin soul connection may be stalled,
but movement is occurring beneath the surface.
So Aries, the god Aries teaches courage without recklessness.
Resist the urge to force communication or demand answers.
So a hidden truth will emerge this month near the end of it.
What appears to be a delay is actually protection.
And I have a sacred message for the Aries in the chat.
The warrior who waits wins battles unseen
because Aries tend to rush into stuff, right?
And so, so, you know, so don't maybe don't rush in.
Okay, so next we have Taurus.
Your patron is Freya.
Freya is the Norse goddess of beauty. She's like a Norse Venus in a certain way. So you're so
Taurus is you know the earth sign. Your tart magnetism intensifies in this month. Old wounds begin
softening. Whether united or separated, the energetic bond grows stronger through appreciation
rather than longing. Prophecy for Taurus is an unexpected gift message or meaningful coincidence
will confirm your path. And the sacred message for Taurus is love flourishes.
where gratitude is planted. Okay, Gemini's, your patron is Hermes Gemini's. Okay, Hermes is, of
course, that he's a god of, you know, Mercury. He can be a god of sometimes deception, but he's a
highly changeable god. He's always shape-shifting and, you know, sometimes duplicity. But so Gemini,
for this month, secretionisties will multiply for you. There'll be dreams, symbols, songs, and a
will become messages. Communication with a twin soul may arrive through unusual channels.
Prophecy for Gemini, a conversation changes your understanding of the connection. Your message
this month is the message arrives where the listener becomes still.
Okay, cancers, cancers, of course, ruled by the moon.
Your patron is Selene, the moon goddess.
And so for cancers, June will awaken emotional healing,
deep memories, surface for release.
Twin soul energies are especially active
during the moon phase.
Prophecy for cancers, a painful chapter
will reach completion, making room for a gentler future.
Sacred message for cancers,
what the tides carry away is never yours to keep.
Leo's, Leo's ruled by the sun. Your patron is raw, the Egyptian god of the sun, you know?
You are being called into visibility. Your twin soul journey is connected to purpose and leadership.
The more authentically you shine, the stronger the connection becomes. Prophecy for Leo's,
recognition arrives through creative expression or public work. A sacred message for Leo's, the sun does not seek permission to rise.
For Virgo's, your patron is the goddess Brigid. It's an Irish goddess.
um okay patterns will become visible you finally understand why certain lessons repeated
june favors healing rituals journaling and practical spiritual work
prophecy for virgos a long-standing confusion dissolves through a simple realization
and a sacred message wisdom will enter through the heart uh wisdom enters through the door
simplicity opens okay okay so libras your patron is aphrodite okay
Relationships will come into balance. If giving too much, you will reclaim your energy. If withholding infection, you will soften harmony because possible through honesty.
Prophecy for Libras. A choice between illusion and unauthenticity will become unavoidable. Sacred message for Libras. True love requires no performance.
We got any Scorpios, Scorpios sign of magic and sex, your patron is Hecate, the Greek
goddess of magic, so the crossroads will be appearing, deep transformation underway, twin
soul connections may trigger shadow work, but the reward is profound empowerment.
For Scorpios, a secret will be revealed, illuminating a hidden path, and your sacred message for
the month is the torch of truth will burn away fear.
Sagittarius
With the patron Artemis, who we saw earlier today, freedom will become the theme.
You're asked to trust the journey rather than the obsess over the destination.
Adventure and spiritual exploration will strengthen this connection.
Your prophecy is travel, learning, or a new spiritual practice will open an unexpected
door.
Secret message for you is the path reveals itself to the traveler.
For Capricorns, Capricorn is my sign, the patron is Saturn, the planet Saturn is the
ruling planet of Capricorn. So if Capricorn's destiny will work through structure,
June rewards us our discipline and long-term vision, twin-soul developments occur through
steady effort rather than dramatic events. Yeah, Capricorns always have to work hard at everything,
Prophecies for Capricorns, a foundation laid months ago, begins producing results. I hope that's
Working on a lot of stuff, right?
Sacred message for Capricorns.
Time will serve those who build with intention.
Aquarius, I'm an Aquarius moon, I'm a Capricorn sun, both first house.
Aquarius, your patron is Prometheus.
He is the Titan who brought fire to man, okay, the creator of mankind.
Revelation will strike like lightning.
Your perspective changes rapidly this month.
Innovative ideas and spiritual breakthroughs are favored, prophecy, a surprising realization.
will free you from outdated beliefs.
Sacred message, the fire of truth cannot remain hidden.
Pisces, you have a patron, Yamaya, okay?
Yamaya, she's like, I think voodoo goddess of water.
So intuition will become especially strong.
Dreams and vision will carry guidance.
The twin soul connection deepens through compassion,
surrender and faith.
So Pisces, a dream or mystical experience
will provide undeniable clarity.
Pisces is traditionally ruled by Neptune
and so he is the god of dreams, right?
Sacred message, the ocean knows the shore
before the wave arrives.
And that concludes our horoscope so the governing deity of june's twin soul energies is my odds
And so we also drew my odd earlier today right in the in butterflies reading so across all the signs the theme is truth before union
So for everybody connections built on fantasy will face reality connections built on authenticity will strengthen
Science synchronize season revelation will increase throughout the month, especially around the full moon
Prophecy for everybody, what is destined cannot be forced, what is forced cannot be destined,
June removes the masks, so souls may recognize one another clearly.
Hope everybody enjoyed. What's up, Easy, how are you? Maya locks me out, so she's like, well,
this is like this flow, right?
Oh, yeah. Well, Maya. So Maya is, yeah. Maya is also in India, right? So they have the Mayans, of
course, in South America, but Maya is like a goddess of illusion, but in a...
She's the same as Lakshmi and Lakshmi like all that if you study Hinduism like it's like, you know, Kali is Shiva
So that that too, but then it's also if you go into the names of the goddesses
Usually they have like the same name like the same name. There's overlaps over what's up easy can someone someone wants to come up
I'll put the link down. We have a chat
Easy's been posting some good stuff lately. I've been looking at his great posts and
You know, so the Amanda Erickson
Maya is also the month of May, maybe.
And so, all right.
But yeah, the goddess was Ma'at
and she's the Egyptian goddess of balance and justice.
And so there's like the 48 laws of Ma'at
or something like that.
And it's all about these intentions.
It's like, you know, Ma'at is also in the underworld.
It's like the justice where our soul goes
and things like that.
I guess if you, she weighs a feather of truth.
She wears a little feather in her hair.
and then the feather of truth is weighed against the heart and whatever is heavier,
the heart is heavier than the feather and you get thrown to like this crocodile kind of creature,
but if you keep your heart light and you don't have regrets, you'll be lighter than the feather
and you'll go on to ascend, you know, lift up. So there's the link if anyone wants to
come on and say hi. I'm going to be great to say hi to somebody.
Because you know, I'm kind of a big um, I'm in the middle of this boycott. I've never seen anybody else even boycotted on YouTube
Well, maybe like less but
You know less is more haha, but uh, yeah, I'm never seeing like such a ridiculous
It's also the most ridiculous boycott to it. It's not really boycott
It's like because most of the people that are even in here probably like
So saying that the boycott so the yesterday there's um money for 20 was in the chat and somebody said money for 20 get out
Of here don't give him a view. Well, first of all, he already gave me the view by being here
Okay, second of all, who is anybody to tell anybody where to go or what to do? I mean, it's like
People need to mind their own business. It's like it's a really interesting that people want this power over other people
I mean, it's like an exact like you know something. That's really. Oh, we have a guess
Okay, hi, okay. I'm not gonna say your name because I
Crystal Marie up here. Hold on a second
Hello, hey, what's up, bro? It's okay. Hey, what's up, dude? How are you branding? What's up, dude?
Hey, wait, I hope you're doing good. How are you?
Yeah
I don't know who that is, but I was like, hi guys.
Oh, I'm good, man.
Yeah, I thought you were on last night.
Good, what's the deal?
What are you doing?
What are you guys talking about?
Well, I just did horoscopes for all the signs.
Like, what's your sign?
If you're doing a sign.
Aquarius.
Oh, you're Aquarius.
OK, I'm in Aquarius Moon.
I'll read Aquarius again real quick,
because they're really short, they're really short,
little monthly horoscopes.
Yeah, yeah, I'm in Aquarius moon. Aquarius is of course, it's ruled by Uranus or also Saturn. It's very close to Saturn, too.
And so, the Aquarius horoscope for this month was, okay, so Aquarius said, revelation will strike like lightning, your perceptive changes rapidly this month, innovative ideas and spiritual breakthroughs are favored.
a surprising realization from you from outdated beliefs
and the fire of truth cannot remain hidden.
I like that for you, because you are a true spreader
but also it says, patron Perrithia.
Perrithia is a really interesting,
he's like a light bringer, he brought light,
he brought fire to man and he got punished for it
but he didn't bring fire to man,
which is like truth at the same time.
So I like that for you.
Oh, we also have another guest.
Oh, Marcy Fox is here.
Hi Marcy.
Hey, what's up?
Hi, how are you?
Good to see you.
I just wanted to hop on really quick.
About to run my mom to the doctor, but oh, yeah
You're on and
Yeah, did you hear your scope? What's here? What's your sign? I'm a Leo, of course. Yeah, I'll read Leo because it's real short
I'll read it quick. Yeah, Leo says
Let's see Leo
said
I'd rather taste
your patron
Patron is raw, who's the Egyptian god of the sun.
It says, you're being called into visibility.
Your twin soul journey is connected to purpose
and leadership.
The more authentically you shine,
the stronger the connection will become.
Recognition arrives through creative expression
and public work.
And the sun does not seek permission to rise.
So there you go.
Yeah, that sounds good to me.
Yeah, at least come by soon because it's been a little quiet here and stuff, but I missed
you and stuff, and I saw you last at the-
I really haven't been on anybody's.
I saw you shortly.
I think it was on my knees for a little bit, and then I think it was on Black North for
a second.
Yeah.
But it's been hitting this for me, so, you know, like-
I've been getting kicked out and hidden in those chats, and it's like that.
Yeah, that's crazy.
Psyche, Psyche, we know who that is, right, with that one.
Yeah, I'm a very controversial, but you know
Going here high on suck is but you're breathing deeply. I don't know who that is. Oh
You can hear me. You can hear me. Oh shit
I'm working on some shit. Okay. It sounded like you're working on some wood. Maybe. Yeah, he does. You're smart. He does. He does like landscaping and stuff. Am I good? Am I good at like identifying sounds? No, I don't know. No, that's a fucking lie. I don't do landscaping. I don't know. Why is it? Why is it dude?
Yeah
Plumbing plumbing water pipes
Am I correct with the shovel noise that is a yeah, I'm digging yeah, yeah, I am digging
I'm digging a big asshole. I'm digging a big asshole. This fucker. This fucker is like
big enough to bury somebody
I'll keep you in mind as a great digger. I don't think I've met you before Brandon
No, hi, I'm nice to meet you. I'm Brandon aka high on high on suck. That's my new alias
Yeah, I know I'm not really bad at reading it says my own stuff
You're coming out of my mouth, but it felt we're going into you
There's a guy named, there's a guy named Hugh Direction that comes by too sometimes.
Nice to meet you.
You're Direction?
Yeah, Hugh Direction.
I gotta do some blending here before I leave, so I gotta make up and get out the door, but
I love you guys.
Love the colors.
Good to see you.
Wow, you too.
Hey, Sig, do you want to come up, Sig?
Love you.
All right, bye.
Nice meeting you.
Have a good one.
Sig said breast.
Oh, Sig, do you want to come up?
You're welcome up today, Sig, if you want to come up.
You know, I miss you.
Hi, baby.
that's a funny name huh hi i'm suck yeah like uh you're that's a funny ass name huh are you
high it's like someone's high on i don't know i just think of like sucking sucking somebody's name
that i saw on my copy day i was like that's a hilarious name yeah i mean they'll do some good
names right here breast holes it's a it's a it's a korean's lady name it's a real name it's a korean
Vicky Cox or there's like or something in Cox and I mean, but it was like this lady's name on Facebook
I was like that a real name. Yeah, you're a lady. I mean, but yeah, we have this huge erection guy that comes here
And we have but I forgot the other guys. I mean he had two names, but yeah, oh, there's Lenore. Hi, baby
You can I have banned you on 36 accounts. Okay, so let me check if I have you banned in my stream
Let me check I heard a Q's cats are dying. I heard they're all sick and fucked up
well that's sad i mean it's like i mean i think isn't he living in his car he shouldn't be having
cats really like you know maybe you stop showing them they said they said why are you even showing
them they look dead that's that's he has a nursing mother he has a cat that's nursing and he does
and he doesn't even feed it right oh
Fuck yeah, I thought you'd love this guy. Oh my god. So yeah, what's what you cute
Please take your cats to like, you know, you you don't have a place for them to live and they're kids pregnant and stuff
And you just please take it to somewhere someone will take it in or something. I mean, it's I mean, please
I mean, it's like how's the cat getting a nurse if it's not even being fed right? You know what I mean?
It has nothing to give. I don't know. I mean, it's like it's terrible
I thought he loved those cats and I'm upset like I'm all he cares about is is being a bum, bro
You're doing better than him. He's a fucking piece of shit. You have your own place. Yeah
I mean, it's like, uh, well, yeah, he moved him with some gay guy at the library
He met and then it's like probably got kicked out of the guy's house after like
Annoying him enough, but um, yeah, so I don't know what's wrong with him and it's like, you know
He certainly should not be like, I mean
The cast looks sick and stuff like that, please please like um
Now that's an animal abuser
And it's like, you know, I get called all kinds of things and stuff, but it's like, it's like, I'm certainly not like, my cats are happy, happy, healthy, they love me.
I feed my cats before I feed myself. I'd rather die than, than, you know, my cats like, you know, go through any kind of suffering.
So Eleanor, like, I don't know, but yeah, it's like, it's ridiculous.
And one of my cat, well, my cat Tux, I don't know if you saw Tux, he's like sleeping in the bedroom right now, but he came back and moved back in.
And he's like, now he's like really cuddly and stuff.
And he like, you know, he did like, you know,
I give him catnip sometimes when you give cats catnip
to get kind of high and then can get a little bit aggressive.
So that's when he like swatted my hand or whatever.
But, and he's like a little bit feral
cause he's been outside for like a year and a half,
but he's healthy.
and he's in here and you know I got my cats all over me like there's Lola
I'm sleeping behind me and then Rudy's on a table like back here he's like
he likes this little table I can see him very well but yeah he's in the corner
right here like sit over there so I got I got four cats and uh you know they're
all taking care of happy healthy and they they do love me and so it's like
don't believe anybody there's a lot of people it's like people will just like
Fucking she's a piece of shit. Look who's saying it dude. She has stocking charges
Posit manufacturing drug charges
Fuckin all kinds of shit. She's a piece of shit, bro
And then like RG's are mod RG's are mod and that dudes from a group that extorts people with their own kids CP, bro
Right, I saw like
On that on that kiwi farmers website. I saw yeah, they posted her show with him on it. They're like looking
He's in this. Oh shit. Really? Yeah. Oh damn and that's recent. Yeah. Well, yeah
Yeah, see and remember that's what I told you remember I said that's what I was gonna do and I never got around to doing it
But I that's what I said Pete. There's people that are hunting these people down, bro
Yeah, because they were saying that they were saying they hate people that are like, you know
Will accuse people of PDF stuff when especially yeah, it's like it's like, you know
It's like because there's a lot of people saying oh like a 40-year-old and a 20-year-old to call that pd
Yeah, well they call them a loggers. That's what they're called. They're called a loggers and that's like what gamble does they just get somebody
And they try to exaggerate every little negative thing about them. They lie about them. Yeah, there's a term for that
It's called a logger. I didn't even know that
And they'll use that term and it's not even that I've been applicable to that that
It's like it's supposed to be for children
Children now they'll say oh, like, you know, if you ever heard of um, Benny Blanco like he actually yeah, you told me about that
Yeah, well, they just lie straight up. They just lie straight up saying oh, he's a pito. They just lie period, dude
I mean Brandon, if there's anything Benny grew me because he taught me how to stream
and I never was interested in him like that, but people will say, oh he looks like a fetus,
he looks like he's a child, he's retarded and all this stuff, he looks like a child,
like his brain is like a child, and so they just exaggerate.
How is he like a child getting drunk and all this and that?
I know he's 25 years old by the way too, it's always like ridiculous.
He looks like a girl, I said he might as well be a girl.
He would get on that, he's like no.
Yeah.
I was telling him he should transition.
Yeah, well, you know, I remember he used to play like, have you heard of Femios? Like, there's someone named Femios.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Femios is talking about him and stuff and like, uh...
Oh, really?
Yeah, and, um, I think he said he, like, was kind of attractive.
I mean, I think he was a mod for Femios, actually.
Like, yeah, he looks more like a girl than that Femios.
That Femios doesn't even, that looks like a dude.
He looks more like a girl than Femios.
Yeah, Femios looks like a Ukrainian guy in a wig a little bit, but...
Yeah.
I've seen some...
There was this transgender I was in...
I was in...
Their chat, their name is...
Their name is...
What is their name?
Sabrina T.W.
And Sabrina T.W.
Shared up with, like, Harvey Fierstein in a...
Like, their ugliest transgender.
And she hated Femios.
And I got kicked out of her chat.
Yeah.
because i would have been me was this chat or something like that but i'm not really have you
seen that other one they're like have you seen that one they're like paranoid uh tasha tilling
it's like some old man oh there's an old man that is he is he a pretty yeah well it's a
trend it's a trend it's a trans but it's like basically an older
They live in a van and they just cry about their case in Florida that oh the judges
Basically, they got a they got charged for like hitting their mom in Florida
And they just keep trying to fight he keeps trying to fight it saying that oh, they're they're working against my rights
Like filing all kinds of different shit to dismiss it and it's like no you can't dismiss it
It says you have a warrant over there and you have to go over there and turn yourself in and go through the fucking court
Bro, you're not gonna get it out of that. Yeah, and just goes on making all these
saying oh look i've had uh uh 60 hearings this and that has been going on for 10 years
oh my my my my yes because you're not special just like everybody else the only way to resolve it
would be to go over there get arrested and then see the fucking judge right it's not the fuck
else you know what i mean yeah like what do you think trying to file all kinds of shit supreme
core dude and everything just gets rejected and they're like look look see they're against me
You're not getting out of it, bro
Love transgender like that. Have you ever seen like that guy?
He's like a man, but he was like in some like store and he's like the guy called him sir
He's like, oh, yeah, that was here. That was at the game. So that was at the game stop over here
It was on the news and shit dude
That was crazy. Yeah, that was over here. Yeah, that's fucking right by my house, dude
I was on the news they interviewed him her on the news and shit
Yeah, I mean like a lot of like a lot of them like because it's like they'll transition like you know way later
Yeah, and so they they're not passable. They've got all the math
They got the biggest look like man, but then now but nowadays there's like plastic surgery
Like there are some trans. Yeah, you would never ever know like oh, yeah, there's some that look good, dude
Amaranth is one of them
Oh, who is nobody even know Amaranth Amaranth really famous like a only fans chick. Okay. Yeah
There's ones that you get sex changes where it looks that it looks like realistic
You know, and it's like, you know, they can actually show it like it looks like I mean you wouldn't be able to tell
But there's really good doctors. I think you have to go to Switzerland with the name to find them. Oh, not Mexico
Mexico is where they get the discount plastic surgeries and it's like I
I feel kind of bad, but you know in order to get a sex change you have to like get
Notes from a psychiatrist like tuned to sign off twice by psychiatrists. Yeah, I should like say they're dick
Yeah, you're crazy basically
Yeah, that's dumb. He should just leave it
Yeah, I mean it's like well, but the thing is it's like you know people they can get it actually like people that have skin down there like you know
That's yeah, they can actually get like you know
They have a lot of skin to work with and so it's better to have skin
But it's like people like there's this one named jazz Jennings who was like started hormone therapy with as a child
Yeah, and it's like and then when she had a sex change she had no skin to work with and so it just like it's like a wound
That keeps popping open and it's like pretty terrible. Oh shit
but but then they do have like the they don't go through puberty so they have the
um they do puberty blockers and so they have like the feminine face but and so it's a really
controversial as to whether like you know yeah people can transition I don't know I'm like I'm
not really I'm not into transgender but I mean I really I don't I don't run into many in my life
you know like hardly any the ones I run into aren't usually that good but there are ones in like music
I think backup dancers were Iggy Azalea and stuff.
And it's like, I'm like, why are these women
like six, four?
And like, I mean, they're beautiful,
but they're like, so, they're so tall.
I mean, this can't be like all women.
I think vegan patriots won.
I think vegan patriot is honestly won, dude.
She has to be.
Well, I mean, I don't know. I mean, it's like I ran into her in Victoria's chat recently and it's like
Oh Victoria
Yeah, well, she's been nice to me. I can't stand that fucking kid. Yeah
Pretty cool though. Big and Patriot like saw I was getting bullied and like and like gave me good advice and stuff like that
What'd she say?
But she said, she said, oh, don't worry about these people.
She's like, I've been through this too many other,
they all this stuff.
But yeah, she wrote me some really nice,
really nice messages and she's been in my chat,
but she hasn't been on the chat.
Oh, she started and she was messaging you?
Oh, what a weirdo, bro, what she did she say anything about me?
No, no, she was just talking about like, you know, like how I was being bullied and stuff
But um, yeah, I didn't they went after her they went after her for being cool with me
Yeah, and I went off on her. I felt bad, but she was doing dumb shit, bro
She was like DM me bro. She's done this multiple times, bro where she starts talking to me, bro
And like acting like she wants to
To come over and meet us be with her and all this and that
But then at the same time like if I don't jump she starts like publicly like glazing other dudes and I knew what she was doing
I was like this chick is trying to trying to force me to be like
Oh, no, I need to grab her now or I need to do this now. So I said fuck that. I told her you're a fucking loser, bro
Doing that shit dude
Yeah, we were cool up until recently cuz she started glazing this dude while she's over here DME
He's saying hey, I might need to go stay with you was that cool and this and that
And then at the same time she's over here like glazing this fucking weirdo dude that dude and on the fucking weird little black nerd
We glasses and an afro dude
the fucking weirdo dude so I said fuck you bitch I said don't ever I said I'm
I said I'm done with you dude okay yeah I mean I want nothing to do with her
after that bro like people like that bro like you're trying to use me get
shit out of me but then trying to kiss other dude's asses I said fuck that bro
and I knew she was doing that on purpose so I get me to like I don't know
Take her more serious or some shit. I don't fucking know
Yeah, that's exactly what she was doing dude, so I said fuck that bro
Yeah, and I noticed it was a pattern. I said, okay, we won't talk for a while
And then she's not talking about any other dudes, but I said the moment we start talking again
She's all of a sudden here talking about all these dudes saying that they're hot
She wants to fuck them and this and that
Like yeah, I know exactly what she's doing, bro. She's trying to get me like to like oh hurry up. I got to go grab her
You know what I mean? Yeah, I don't give a fuck. I mean, I've watched so I told her I said
Yeah, yeah, I watched her stream and she was like, you know, basically it was just like she was
In the bathroom doing her makeup and it was just like her dog in like a tutu like sleeping on a bed
She's now she's fucking in sleeping in a car. She's homeless again
Yeah, I kind of saw that she chose it. She had like a shower curtain as her wall right now
But you know, I do with yeah, she got the $20,000 donation though, you know, that was pretty so that's so that's so funny
Dude, yeah, no, it was over time, bro. I was over time. I thought the guy said he was gonna die
It was like it was like it was like $2,000 every month bro for like fucking
Six months or some shit. You wanted it back. No, he just talked shit about it. Yeah
but
Yeah, dude, she's fucking oh, and I found out her mom got arrested in math and you for new math in New Mexico, dude
So I started to see so she fights with her mom saying that her mom's jealous of her that she's all oh my mom's jealous of me
Cuz I'm getting to go out West and have fun and party
And I'm like what the fuck your mom already did that apparently
Long before you
Vegan patriot and her mom well
They're from Ohio, but I guess at some point, she was born in Scottsdale, Arizona, or they
lived in Scottsdale, Arizona at some point and then moved back to Ohio, but on her mom's
court records in 2001, she was arrested for two felonies in Clovis, same town, clumsy
Yeah, he's a bitch dude. I go to me bro. I could go to McDonald's right now, bro
Yeah, he wants me to get swatted dude
That's why he's doing that cuz he knows gamble or somebody will just call the cops, bro. You like yeah, yeah
Fuck that dude. He was about it. He would just come to my house
Right
He's really silly. I mean, it's like, yeah, I mean, he like was like blazing me a lot when he started
Yeah, he started getting popular, screaming and stuff like that and like and he would always come to my show and like be like
Oh, I'm gonna donate to you. You're so cool. Like I think it's probably my show. It's won't you find this out
Who said that?
Homzi
And then oh, yeah, he's fake
And then it's like now he's like fuck you, you know, you're
That dude's a child abuser how a child abuser calling somebody an animal abuser
The fucking child abuser bro, and then they always go no he didn't abuse it
He didn't abuse him bro abuse is abuse if you didn't abuse a kid you wouldn't have been convicted of it
You know what I mean?
They act like you get charged for abusing kids even though it's not really child abuse like no
That's not how it fucking works, bro
You get charged and convicted of child abuse when you're found to be abusing a fucking child, bro
That's how it fucking works. Yeah, even Chris K was telling him he's all right. Yeah in prison. He's all there wouldn't be no excuse
There wouldn't be no let me explain this and that know it just be automatic, bro. Yeah automatic, you know
I mean, there's no oh, let me explain and I'll know
That's why there's no explaining because then because then anybody could do that somebody could have a
Molestation charge. I'm like, no, let me explain. You know what I mean? No, it doesn't work like that, bro
Yeah, he wasn't PC when he was in prison he wasn't PC. They that's when he got raped
Yeah, that's fucking I think he got raped. I think he got raped in PC by another PC
Well, I mean it's like they'll put them in PC with like snitches and then somebody'll be like a snitch or like a gang drop out
And they'd be like, oh you're a child abuser and then they'll do something to them
So even PC's not safe, you know what I mean? Yeah
I mean, yeah, I didn't do that. And so it's like, you know, that's, I mean, that's, it's like, uh, if there's really discouraged people, I mean, or I hope it would discourage it. But I mean, it's like, I can't believe people will still do that kind of stuff.
And it's like, it's kind of unimaginable to me. I just like, it's like, so sick.
Oh, yeah. Now I see the news. People get arrested on sick fuckers, dude. I just saw a video today. Some dude got arrested for filming shit with his daughter, dude. Sick fuck, dude.
Yeah, the girls the girls older sister saw it on the on the iPad dude and went to the cops dude
Fucking sick fuckers, dude
Well, it's like that's it. Well, it's good like, you know, now there's more like, you know, people are like, you know
They're creating evidence for themselves. It's like that and I mean, it's dark web thing
It's like the dark web is just like run. I mean, it's like it says it's safe or whatever
But it's that's where they get it. It's all a setup. It's all a setup all those things
That's the cops fucking all that's all it is is the cops waiting for people to get caught dude. Yeah, so that shit is dude
And I'm like, it's kind of funny, like it's like people fall for it, but, um, yeah, um...
Yeah, there is a camera, but it's like I finally this society is like and I think people are so sick in the society because the
Society is almost encouraging it and it seems like yeah, we're getting like so
It's like, you know you like you said something about virtue signaling and it's like that it's become such a virtue signaling topic now
Where it's like becoming so exaggerated and now it's like because it's being addressed
Everybody like literally almost everybody here on YouTube on this community is in YouTube is like a hues of it or something like that
Yeah
that and it's like it's like it's losing all meaning and it's like that's really
negative for the people that are really being abused and some of the animal
abusers it's like you can't if they call people that didn't
neuter their cat or somebody that let's their cats go outside animal abusers.
Yeah.
It's like how many, how many millions of people are called animal abusers?
I mean, it's like, yeah, from people that are actually like, you know, torturing
animals and, you know, it's like, so, it's like, so fucked up.
It's like, yeah, crystal and that's torture cutting off your cat's fingers.
Yeah.
I mean, that's one of the worst things you can do is declaw a cat.
I mean, that is just like, yeah, it's basically cutting off their fingers.
They cut off like.
The cutting off be like a human cutting off the tops of your fingers
What am I lying about? She's saying that I'm lying. Yeah, right BS. What's BS? I think she was what's BS?
I don't know if she wants to she wants to address it
I think what's so BS
Was that something about the vegan Patriot stuff? I think that's when she
What is BS? Yeah, I don't lie, bro. I don't make up shit, dude
Yeah, I mean it's like I I've seen like you know you you do back up most like the stuff you say with like, you know
Usually, you know, you see your videos and yeah, and good information and
And I, yeah, I just know that, I mean, but I've seen stuff about gamble that it's like so shocking and it's like, and then for him to be like, you know, so like, oh, I don't think he's like really lauded anymore, but at one point I guess he was like getting a lot of
Everybody dude every famous streamer basically did everyone is that was it was the one stream?
Oh, yeah, and then the one streamer that he said he's all this is the only streamer
I could stomach and he was trying to buddy up to him and that's Amaranth's husband Nick Lee
Who is known like he literally goes live like abusing her her screaming climb the cops?
And he's all he's all this is the only streamer. I could stomach and then I ran him out of that community
I kept going in a Nick Lee's discord server and telling Nick Lee. I was like, hey, you know this dude's a creep, right?
And he got fired of it broke tired of it and he finally left dude. I ran gamble out of that dudes community
So where is he now like I because he keeps I think he was was he really in the chat yesterday
I mean, I didn't see the chat yesterday, but oh, no, it was all yeah
that all that was either him or is
Australian mess head buddy that he had turned on before and now they're buddies again the one that was simping for the girl
He raped
My god, yeah, the Australian it was either him or it was either him or gamble, dude
They make it too obvious, bro. They still all say the same shit, dude
Yeah, yeah, you can bring in a people that nobody knows about bringing up certain names and shit dude like
Yeah, I mean it's like I just don't like it. I mean it's like when I was in like
I guess Christmas cat like a month ago or something and he was there and he
Started attacking me and calling me an animal abuser and blah blah blah blah and it's like
And it's like I'm someone that declutter cats and
Yeah, his own cat killed itself, bro. He had a cat running and it fucking killed itself, dude. Oh my god
Yeah, dude, how do you imagine having your own cat killed itself, bro? What does that tell you dude?
that's sad
Yeah, so anyway, I mean it's like yeah, I think I think you know, it's just like
Once but yeah once these people are pointed out like you know, especially usually people that are accusing people of other things
It's like it's like they're trying to like get attention from themselves because it really like a lot of times they're like they're
Like especially of all the virtue signaling like the gamble does but it's like you can just tell he's like trying to
I mean it's like
People just like I guess a lot of people just don't want to listen or like, you know
They want to but it's like, you know really I mean things are out there that are like, you know
Showing exactly that's a small group of people bro. It's never gonna be like all the masses. Oh everybody, you know what I mean? No
It's a small, small group of people, you know what I mean?
Right, that are actually like doing that, but not everyone wants to be like in that group or like in the crowd or whatever, I heard them talking about it.
We want to get it in our group and then we can like, you know, accuse everyone else of doing it and we'll come to our group so they don't get accused of it or something like that.
Yeah, exactly.
It's so weird, it's like, and so yeah, I'm glad I'm not in like, I'm not really, I'm not a joiner, and I'm, I just care about the truth, I really care about the truth and it's like, you know, it's like,
And it's like also like if there's things I call victimless crimes where there's no one here who are exploited in the situation and so
I'm more of a libertarian where it's like I think people should have freedom
But it's like as long as they're not hurting other people then you know people can do what they want
But um, yeah, I mean the world's crazy right now. Yeah, like gamble. He's a sick one, bro
There's literally multiple girls and I have all their testimonies bro
That they he went to them when they're weak suicidal getting out of the mental hospital
and tries to exploit them.
This girl named Rory, bro, he raped her, gave her drugs,
threatened to swat her.
Although he did swat her, swat her,
doxx her, harass her, stalk her, sending her drugs.
A girl named Rory. Yeah, just the land are like these like you can tell they're kind of weak-minded people just because it's like
I used to see how the guys are able to tell them what to do and they're like
They're like looking for someone to tell them what to do or something like that like I see yeah
He was telling her oh have this person I've had this person don't have any she would just like bring him back up
Or this whatever he said and then he was yeah automatically. Yeah, he's poor mommy
Yeah, she's a follower no brain of her arm. That's why she's not supposed to be online
Right. I mean, it's like, yeah
That's why she doesn't go live on her own shit because her parents watch it, dude
That's why now she only goes live on other people's panels
Yeah, I haven't seen I mean, I haven't even seen her recently. I mean, it's like I saw her recently
but uh, yeah, but with Q up there and stuff and
It's like, you know, she had like some people in her chat at first, but it's like it looks like it's died down
Yep, dead dead dead, dude
I mean it's like I'm so I mean I always well I mean it's like I'm lucky I always like you know
I will have people that that uh that support me and stuff and and really do know the truth and
stuff but it's like it does seem like I but I didn't lose like a lot of people that were just like
But there were trolls anyway, and so I don't even give a fuck.
Like, I'm like, it opens up room for better people to come in.
And I've met some already better people who have come in and new people,
and they're not getting chased away by these trolls.
But with RG thing, let me see.
They also said...
Yeah, they hate like they're like, oh, well, he's the kind of guy that he just does all these doorknocks and and like you know
I mean that's like that's all they do and and oh, yeah
And so, you know, I'll example several months ago the guy is his his real identity and stuff and I had this I was like
I don't know and then when I saw I went on the
Kiwi farms. They had his picture
The guy it's like that picture that you were showing the face and he's walking pig
It's like, oh, yeah, it all makes sense now. It's like, yeah, and then he's still trying to deny it
He's noticed that he's still trying to deny it, bro. It's there's pictures of you walking your fucking dog
Yeah, I mean it's quite obvious and then it's like I've been now that I've gone back and listened to like the guy's voice
Yeah, it's it's it's it's definitely he has the same cadence and he just puts on a little a little diss right here
I think I was like, I don't know, you know, but um, yeah, and he's like
Yeah, I guess he's been he's been pretty quiet lately. I've just seen him in Kate's and like, you know, he hasn't been like so
So out like he's I heard you when you call it when you called into Sam Man's show saying you're a Theo
And he and you came on and you said I'm gonna I'm gonna dox rg and and um, and and then everyone's like, who is that like no one
Yeah, like they couldn't figure it out, but I
Yeah, it's pretty funny like I was like, I knew this but um, yeah, Sam Man's kind of slow and uh
I don't know. He's like, he's weird. He's like, oh, he doesn't want to even, he won't, he's afraid he'll get in trouble.
So he's like, he won't, even if you're in the clip, he won't like, he'll try to like not, like not put you in it and stuff like that.
And so I say, oh, yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, he was restreaming for fucking this, the panel with Alex.
And once I started restreaming him, he turned it off. Yeah. Fucking loser.
Oh yeah. So RG, he fucking
He was trying to deny it bro, and it's like bro. He look bro. He lives in Santa Cruz, California in the woods
He literally lives in the fucking woods. He doesn't have a single fucking neighbor, bro
In a cabin little tiny. I don't even think there's a house there. He lives like in a tent or some shit, bro
Yeah, I mean I think I saw like a they had an aerial view or something like that
And it would look like it's some kind of like all these cars parked around there
But I didn't see any like house or there's just like yeah, there's like no house like it's yeah
It's like in the middle of the woods, but there's no house though. Yeah, it was kind of there's no house
And when you look it up, there's only property. There's no yeah
They don't like them. I mean they don't like them over there
And it's like that's those are people that are called like they call themselves like you know
We're into like the low cows, but they they even have like a you know ethics and stuff like that
I was like, oh, they're not it's not really that bad
Because they're kind of going after like real like real weird like really fucked up people and that actually and they have
You know standards and stuff like that. It's not it's not actually a bad website, but um
But I wasn't on it, but he certainly is and you can go search of his name and it's all over there
Yeah, that's why music biz Marty didn't like him because fucking they do shit like that
That's why they were banished by the whole internet. Nobody like they all went hiding too. Yeah, and Martin hiding
I met Marty before he died like right before he died I met Marty and Jamie Rose and they were like and then
I think he came over because he heard like oh look this guy's kind of weird
And but then he like ended up liking me a lot and I would do sports betting with him. Okay. Well, thanks Brandon
I guess he disconnected, but, um, yeah, I mean, it's like, you know, but, you know, again,
like, you know, he's saying, like, you know, RG has said terrible things about me recently. And,
you know, it's like, look, it's like, you know, people, people are trying to get the attention
off of them so much. It's like, you gotta maybe like wonder why, you know, and I'm just an easy
target, I guess, right now, because I'm like, nice. And, uh,
I don't know. Yeah, living like Ted Kaczynski. Yeah, I mean, it's like the unabomber, right? He was an interesting character
So let me see what I mean
I was watching something I was watching this thing about the you know
Google's like, you know releasing like all these millions of mosquitoes and stuff. What happened to Jamie Rose?
You never see her. Okay. Okay, Brandon. You're always welcome back
Jamie Rose was actually she came a couple months ago and she was on the show and saying hi and everything
I think she's like a little bit less on the internet
I know she was really like, you know,
heard over like the Margie thing inside about that.
And I don't think, I don't know if she's around as much.
Lenore for president?
Yeah, Lenore for president.
You should see Tux.
I mean, he's in the bedroom right now.
He's sleeping on the bed, but he's doing good.
Let me see if I have anything to show.
Like I think that this is,
oh, there's Brandon, I think, let me see.
Okay.
Yo.
Clicked out, I don't know what the fuck happened.
It says, oh, rumor is that Q from Pittsburgh to California
moved closer to me?
Oh, no, I don't think so.
I think he just wanted to go to California.
He had California dreams, but he moved him with some gay.
He had some Greek gay guy, and then I
think he got kind of kicked out or something like that,
because.
You know, he will that that woman be be like he destroyed her house like it
Like you see like it was like he left it all like, you know
There's all these drugs and fucking everything's like dirty and and destroyed and like that
She like let him live there and like and then uh kicked him out
And then he was in the tent with the homeless guy sleeping in some time with an Indian guy
And then like he left his bag and he maced the guy
Why would you sleep in a tent with a homeless dude?
Well, cuz he was in the homeless camp at that point yeah, but it doesn't make sense like what do you need the tent for bro?
Like but another man
You know what I mean like it doesn't make sense, bro
If I went homeless today, bro, I'm not going and hey guys, I mean sleeping your tent with you. What the fuck dude
Well, it looks like a big fucking weirdo. I didn't mean camp everyone's probably just like
Probably nobody's very sleepy very much probably just like, you know
Skrull in the pookie to pookie in that 10. Oh, yeah, dude. Yeah, he's still doing it
Look how fucking oily he is fucking dirty bastard
He's a fucking meth head, bro, and I can't wait till he gets another job. I took his last job, dude
Anybody that drinks 30 beers in a night is probably like on some kind of like other drug because it's like that's like yeah
Yeah, because you pass out and that's like me bro last night
I got I passed out after one hour bro of drinking last night
Passed out. Yeah, it's like I yeah, but I can drink like that now
I drink like one like you know one or two like you know eight percent alcohol drinks and that's like plenty for me
Call Chris K and vitamin probably have his number. He was on Tommy James earlier. Oh, it's hilarious. Do you have Chris K's number?
Brandon
Or do you know how to get a hold of Chris K? I don't know Chris K is funny, but yeah
I haven't seen him in a while. I haven't seen him in a while
He used to come over here he was he'd tarot readings for some for some people sometimes his readings were better than others
I'm a he's an interesting tarot reader. It's a little bit unconventional. So reality Nancy. What am I lying about? Who am I lying about?
I don't know which that's it. Oh, I don't know what she meant by it. But um
Does anybody know how to get a hold of this game? I was a friend's on discord with them, but I have a new discord
I'm not connected to him anymore
But if you I don't know I'll look up his phone number because yeah, I heard he got he got a victim from his house
And oh, he's been live. He was live at a house. He was alive at a house at the same house
Just fucking oh last night. He's oh, yeah
He's going in a Tommy James's panel fucking a good times last night. Yeah, he might not like
He might have been on Clumsy's talking shit about me. I don't know. Oh, yeah, he was saying. Oh, yeah
Yeah, he's lives. He's at the same house, dude
You're saying oh Clumsy you're not gay or something like that and it's like yeah
He's like it. He's gay. I mean he's he's like, you know, just or not gay, but maybe bisexual because he got beat up by a midget
Bro, and then he oh, yeah, he was acting like he don't know me, bro
Me and him and Wappy flanker used to talk every day, bro
Like all day, dude, like I'd be at work and I'd just be talking to them, bro
Yeah, he's full of shit, dude
It just means you can't see what he types. It doesn't mean he can't see what you type
He's probably in stream yard, and so that shows all the comments, too
Yeah, yeah, I've heard of that wappy flanker before though
Yeah, and if you're gonna block me Nancy you better keep my fucking name out your fucking mouth, then oh
Cuz I don't like that people saying shit about me, and I can't see what they're saying
I'm gonna take that as an action
But against me, you know what I mean?
I'm going to take that like, hey, I'm plotting on you, but I don't want him to see.
You know what I mean? That's all I'm going to take it as, dude.
I don't think he's plotting on you, but it's like, you know, it's like, there's just like, you know, there's a lot of.
Let's see, do you know the exam and his mom made love?
I mean, I don't think so.
I'm not gonna say that.
I mean, it's like, you know,
I know Sam and it's kind of slow,
but I'm not gonna say that.
I don't really want to talk,
I wouldn't talk about people like people's family
and stuff like that, you know, rest your soul.
You know, I'm not Q or it's like,
I'm gonna say like, you know,
put a picture of his mom and stuff as my profile picture.
I mean, I think that's fucked up.
And it's like, but Sam and didn't really care
when Vito was doing for me.
So, yeah, yeah fucking people like that. It don't matter dude people like that deserve it, bro
What's up with all this fucking basketball shit in New York like what the fuck? I don't know is there
Game I don't fucking know I thought there's one how many fucking games is there? Oh, there's big back Kate in the chat
What was it? Hey big back? Hey? Hey Kate? Hey? Hey when I get around to it. I'm gonna start your job is gonna be gone Kate
Okay, well, that's not the real Kate. I don't think I'll make sure you call yourself. Oh
But yeah, no, I know she does watch and stuff like she's like she's like been on my ass because she's like
And she's telling people not to watch my show but then she
Yeah, tell people not to watch it, but then saying it go over here and watch it
There's people
Well, seriously, I know that the point is it's like if I was to get into what Kate's asked and she would run
Yeah, the show wouldn't she and so it's like so saying that I don't run my own show or somebody else
I do decide who comes on and so it is my show and and you know, and so
I don't know what people are talking about. They're just like ridiculous. There's I don't I don't listen to what people tell me what to tell me to do
I have my own decisions and so yeah pressure
Because yeah, why are we gonna listen to them look at the people they have there they have people that are worse
So why are you gonna listen to them exactly that makes no sense?
It's all because they don't like me because they're beef and you know what started all bro because I've basically gone to every single
Every single freaking uh all these streaming. I just talked shit to him, bro. That's why they all don't like that's why it was so easy for them
To all say yeah, fuck him. Yeah, you know what I mean? Yeah, there's already dude when the shit with vegan patriot hat bro Blake
I would just go to different streams and be like uh-huh. You're a loser. You know what I mean? That's why they all don't like me, bro
Yeah, that's just now they have bullshit to try to throw at me. You know what I mean? Yeah
Like in the
Seriously, I don't think the stuff that people say about me is true and they throw it at me constantly
So it's like, you know, it's like I understand like just being slandered and why and why they do it and like like they're
They're trying to get attention from themselves or attention for themselves. We're trying to steal people's audience
We're trying to look like we're good guys or good people. Yeah all that stuff and it's like
I'm so lame and obvious that uh, yeah, I just don't I mean I really I really have become a lot
stronger through these situations where it's like, you know, it's like I'm glad I I'm not giving into
like pressure and like, you know, oh my god my view it's like I didn't say that I like to do it and
it's like I'll do it if I like to do it and it's like it's not like it's not like I rely on this
for money and stuff like that maybe people don't because oh he
He didn't dox anybody. He's never doxed one person on my panel. Who's saying that? Who's saying that?
That JB person at Brandon and psyche the new panel verse power couple they are mad and then it's like
Oh, it says maybe people don't chat because Brandon doxes people on your panel. That's JB 57458 or something like that
But yeah, no Brandon's Brandon's a good guy like it's like I could I just like you know
I could just tell that it was like there's something more to it than
People are saying they had such a reaction and it's like it's such a like oh you better do this you better do this and I think we're gonna
Like you know get everyone and it's like they took out the trash of my chat really it's like there's
And like bothering me and I can never get rid of his name is oh pulling it. I don't know anybody's name
Who who who's being done nobody's being doxxed fucking idiot
See he did well if that's sure then you just dox that person. Yeah, you're yeah, who said that this was anybody's dox
You did so he's doxing
So who's doxy? Yeah
See see how they work they dox themselves dude look JB to the sea. He's doxing. Yeah
Maybe there's no doxing my chat. I have to move you because you're doxing my chat
It is
I mean, it's like you're like it's called it's all dry snitching, right? It's like yeah
Yeah, you know
Yeah, how would you know? Yeah, what the fuck? How would you know what the fucking mom's name is dude?
That's why oh, bro
That's crazy, dude. No, people are allowed to eat like pretty much like even like an even saying a name is not
There's phone numbers
And even if and even if bro isn't crystal and gambles her husband, right?
So who is she to cry bro if her mom were to get Docs bro because her idol is gamble, bro, right?
Is he and he's a doctor, right? Yeah. Oh, yeah, bro
He does everything under the Sun bro all that shit, bro
Like really the people are
Everybody is like seems to be attached like salmon and yeah, I mean, I I like Zia, but you know
It's like, you know, he's controversial in that people are saying the same exact stuff and it's like but it's like yeah
There's a problem with people you know, yeah, and you know, it's funny now is now they don't ban me in his chat now
Now they don't ban me do that's funny. I thought I'm not allowed nowhere. I thought I'm not allowed nowhere. You know what I mean?
Yeah, the only place. I'm not allowed is set is Samans and betas
Yeah, oh Tommy all these other people I wouldn't even consider them because they're fucking
Nobody's bro. Like what the fuck I don't go to those palm of James. Oh, you're not you know, you're not allowed nowhere
What do you mean nowhere? You mean fucking salmon and betas fucking shit. What do you mean? No where that's not
Nowhere, bro
He just loves them because you have more people in the chat than him. I can't wait till Tommy James dies, dude
Well, yeah, I don't think it'll be very long. His foot looks like it'll fall off. It'll be it'll be soon, dude
His foot is like disease. He said he got in a fight, but it looks like it's like no he's a liar
No, no, it's that shit. It's when you inject fentanyl for some reason it just does that dude your your extremities
They that happens dude
Yeah, it's still unknown why they don't even know why bro, but yeah, look at all the homeless people, bro
there's people with like
Fluids leaking out of there like ankles and shit dude and it's rocks and you could see bandages over it with like the liquid
Coming through soaking through and shit, dude, and they I was threw up. It was so gross. He's like, oh, yeah
Or something like that
Yeah, that's like walking up with a rotting off arm bro. Like you got bit by a fucking
Rattlesnake. Yeah, look guys. I got in a fight
My arms rotting off
Would you get in a fight with would you get in a fight with a fucking Gaboon viper?
I know
Tell me jim is walking around like Oregon or something
Like the eight mile. I'm an eight mile. I'm a gangster
It's a punk, bro
He's a fucking punk, dude. I agree. Yeah, why is crystalline? Why would crystalline cry about doxing?
She's she's pro gamble DX
That was their whole thing about doxing streamers, bro. That was like their little
That was their little four. Yeah, we doxxed. That's why it's called DX
So if he could do it if he could do it I could do it too
You know what I mean? If he could do it then anybody could do it and they could still be a good person
Right because Gamble such a good hero, right? Oh, yeah, and then they're all saying comes all I like the work
He does he does good work. What the fuck is he done?
What is what has he done? He hasn't done shit, bro
Yeah, he has never done anything bro, and he doesn't even extort them. He just talks she just threatens him
Yeah, he doesn't get nothing from him. He doesn't get shit
That's kind of like that
That's kind of like the suicide coercion almost everybody hates him bro like how they talk about RG and all those people
Yeah, him is the same thing every that's he can't even go outside, bro
Yeah
People aren't looking for me to unalive me people are looking for him
You know what I mean, right? I don't have to worry about coming outside every day dude. He does
He's messed with people that have money bro foosie
What kinds of people hate him Aiden raw oh Aiden Ross?
Everybody bro. Everybody dude people with money and bodyguards and security hate him dude
I'm having a look at something you see
Yeah, so gamble is on it looks like he's on the this Kiwi Farms website, too. It's uh, oh, yeah, they say he's a pedo
Yeah, it says a pedo, huh? Yeah
This is a known doctor in pedo says he's it says that's the dude who pushed fousy over the edge by lying about sending the girl
Fousy was fucking as a double agent. He has only claimed to fame
The gamble is the one old fousy threatened to kill and ended his career over prides himself on trolling retarded
Of course boring idiot who claimed fousy blame fousy for losing his twitch channel
I mean, I mean, it's yeah, but he's all he's all over the kiwi farms and stuff like that. And so, you know
On ip2 it calls him a pedo. It says yeah
IP2 thread there's a thread about ip2. Oh
Yeah, and then that's where I also learned all these people said I'm such a piece of shit
On that thread, it shows like everything that Attila's done, everything Trisha Licious has done.
Bro.
Those are bad people, bro.
It says, Gamble, the same Gamble I assumed was interviewed by Callie, the Aaron Carter Gamble.
Server and Happy, our killstream crew is mentioned as people who have now joined the plate game.
Have you heard of the plate game?
Yeah, they don't like them. Yeah, they discarded them. They don't like them either now.
Okay.
It says the fucking and recharge is nothing but a burden to society his antics are nothing
Yeah, a new than anyone he hides been a fucking imaginary wall. He calls mental issues
Yeah, he does nothing but attention whoring being a menace wasting resources and edge lord dick stroking. Yeah
Don't know. I mean, it's like yeah, you can yeah, you've been doing this shit for years and somehow nothing happens to him
I don't know. It's they see it's like and he he also swatted down
Yeah
Well, I have him on video swatting me bro
I could technically sue the cops bro because I could say this dude's on video swatting me
You didn't do anything about it and you're causing
It's causing me harm, you know what I mean?
And you're not have didn't do anything to protect me bro when that's your fucking job, bro
Right, I mean it's like the police, you know what I mean, but it's like really like the people that were there's a bunch of people on tape doing it
Like they're saying oh my god. I have my name is Brandon. I have a gun
I'm gonna yeah, yeah the way the law works the way the law works is all those people involved right there are all culpable
That's the way the law is dude, but they didn't do shit, right?
I know. Well, it's like, you know, it's like, yeah, police are supposed to be protected.
Well, who knows? Maybe they are. I can't say what they're doing.
APD told me that the FBI is dealing with it, not them.
They said that the FBI told them to just send it all to them, so.
Yep, and I know that yeah, it's been the community asking about RG and stuff, too
And yeah, like they started getting arrested I guess that all that you know
I don't know the whole story about how Tony got a rest
You know why the Tony it said it said like cyberbullying and like yeah, and then I told him I was our ha ha
You got arrested. He's all you know the guy that he's all you know that guy that the guy that pressed these charters on me
Got raped, right?
That's what that's what he said dude
Like so what the fuck so yeah, that makes it worse bro, that's what yeah, that's why you're being arrested
No, I'm just saying like what the fuck
He was actually like a RG's low cow and they used to make him drink toilet water and like
Like we have a selfie
And they never accepted him kind of and so that's why yeah, yeah
Me trying to like get acceptance too early because it would have been done to him
So he was trying to do it to me or something like that, but it's yeah all he is. I mean, it's like he really
All they do is the same shit like they do the same shit to everybody. They're like, oh, let's just like send like, you know
Scrap metal people are or send manure
And it says that they're scared to swat that they call it swat light
That's what they did that other friday on on me. That's why the cops came because it was different
Yeah, because usually they won't even come. It's a federal felony, you know, and yeah
They were like they were like calling they were like calling and just saying that some guy was like screaming running around
Nothing that was dangerous. You know what I mean? Yeah
And so they came in there. Oh, they said that they said that you were like dancing on the cars naked and
This and that like what the fuck
Even that can be dangerous
Like somebody like yeah, I mean it's like that's really fucked up because people can get killed over that still a hoax call
They'll still look in it's probably still a felony. Yeah. I mean, yeah, I'm supposed to hoax. Yeah, it's a hoax. Oh, yeah
We miss
This is in a services police services
Yeah, so it's like you know people should really like just mind their own business and like you know people live and let live
And it's like you know if you're not
Why
Just going after innocent people that can be considered like weaker
or something, but it's only the weak people that attack the weak, right?
Or else they're on their own size, but they're afraid to, right?
They're only going to pick on somebody they perceive that they're going to mess with the wrong person, eventually, right?
And then, you know, it's all going to catch up to them, even if it doesn't, like, legally.
A little by karma, and, you know, some special place in hell, you know, I'm sure.
I mean, it's like...
All this negative energy even like they were sending people from like two hours away
Like it's like a 80 year old Mexican lady looking for like a weeb
Stuff like that. It has to drive four hours and just think about all that negative energy
They're generating that goes right to them that goes right to them. And so they probably have health problems
They probably have all kinds of legal issues. Yeah one time they did that one time
They had somebody ordered pizza to my house, bro. It was some lady
She looked all tweaked out broke his fuck dude in it and she had a van and it was full of like little like
Little kids bro like four-year-olds five-year-olds six-year-olds
Yeah, so fucked up and she said that she had been waiting. She had said that she had been waiting there for like an hour, dude
Oh my god. Yeah, and then it's like yeah
I had a piece of lady come to my door three times in a row because he kept texting her saying oh
I'm gonna give you a big tip back and he'll give you the money and I'll be like no
I told you like yeah already twice and she keeps coming to the door and then he's like oh knock real loud on the door and
Stuff like that and it's like I mean it's just got like so ridiculous, but um, you know
It's like, uh, but he's, you know, it's like, you know, I think that arrest did it.
And I think he's like, maybe learned, but it's like, he keeps, he keeps saying,
Oh, well, psychies do for some more concrete and blah, blah, blah.
I just gave the concrete to my friend and he like carried it to his car.
And it was a good day.
It's like, I can give it away pretty easily.
I mean, it's like, so.
it's like not even like it's just like it didn't even bother me I felt more sorry for the people
that he was wasting time with you know or wasting their time and like people that he was sending
over that had nothing to do with anything that's the real victims in the situation really I mean
it's like yeah but there are like there was like a black guy that came and wanted to beat me up and
because he was like he drove to get something for free and then it's I didn't have anything he thought I was like doing it to
Like fuck with people and then yeah, but it's my neighbor had to like you know calm him down and stuff
But he did was it that same neighbor that broke your window or what it might have been because that was the guy that
was
I ran into him like actually yes, and he just like we just sit in
To each other we just like walk by but I have my window fix already and I don't know I think I think he's
Probably probably feels embarrassed to go from like across the street. I think she's like, you know, like all like freaked out about it and stuff because
Yeah, I picked it and stuff and it's oh, yeah
Yeah, it's just fucked up people how much is the random month over there. I might move over there, dude
Well, I mean it's california. This is close to the beach by there. So there's different
You know, it varies, but um, you know, it can be kind of expensive around here like 3 000. Yeah, I mean, it's like yeah, it can be like up to that
Yeah, I mean it's like uh, you know, it uh
But depending on if you're facing the ocean or not and stuff like that my family owns all kinds of apartments, too, bro
My grandpa's a real estate tycoon. Yeah
My grandpa's how a Jewish so bro he used to rent me out a piece of shit place, bro
Yeah, it was a fucking piece of shit. I was like damn, bro. You want money from you want money for this, bro?
God damn
Very fucking piece of shit, dude
Yeah, well, I'm pretty lucky to live here like my dad did like
special because it's like it's like right in the middle of like where I can like walk everywhere and I you know
Yeah, I'm closer to the family and and I could I could be here and like you know
She's always worried that I would it's something would happen to me because I've been I have been victimized that people before and it's like
They try to fuck with me and like stuff and so you know, it's like if I didn't have like a
Help I mean I was like I wouldn't be able to like survive because
Um, yeah, but I'm lucky I have like a family knows me. They love me and uh, you know, that's really all it matters. It's like
Um, they're they don't care about tools on youtube, but they mean they they hate these people that that fuck with me
Yeah, don't even tell them about them bro. Don't even fucking say shit, dude
I don't but it's like, you know, the day like the neighbors were complaining and stuff because you know, there's like these weird
for scrap metal and stuff and it's like
And it's like, what are you doing to provoke these people?
I'm not provoking them.
I'm not doing anything.
They're psychotic, like crazy people that just like,
they're the stuff with people.
And it's like, fortunately, it's like, what the hell?
Sorry.
I'm like, there's a guy that chainsaw outside.
We can look at the gardeners over here.
Hey, Lola.
Come here.
He's my kitty, Lola.
Lola, come here.
That's funny.
Anita Blunt was saying, oh, we could still get him evicted.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's his that's his only friend list
That's his only friend. What's that's all that's the only person he has. What is it?
Thank you, but if I were being here good to see you. Is rain here or is it rain?
Hey, raise the rain. Can you come up rain?
This is Lola. So yeah, so if you guys haven't seen tux yet
He's in the bedroom right now, but he was on the stream earlier now
He's like he's really sweet and he's like he's like used to being here and so he's kind of move back in
That's Lola right here. She's tricks his mom and she's a really sweet cat
Know you have a really cute cat, too. I don't believe one cat or two. Yeah
I have one cat. Yeah, just one Siamese cat that I rescued
yeah from my ex she was a
She was the stain of me and shittie, but she wasn't taking care of the fucking cat
Bro, she fucking didn't feed when I met her bro. She had its litter boxes overfilled
Didn't didn't feed him did nothing dude. Yeah, that's sad, you know, it's like
Yeah, well my cats have a cat door. I have a like a little cat door they go in and out of and so they don't even like you know
They don't mean to really use use the litter box in here
But you know the people are like oh my god
I bet his house smells like piss and you know those cats
You guys catch mice, you know, they like to play with mice.
Yeah.
They don't eat them.
They're not starving for mice.
They like play with them until they die,
then they take out the body and bury it or something like that.
You know, it's like, it's like, it's like so natural,
but it's like, they act like it's like.
No, they eat it.
They eat it.
No, they eat it, bro.
That's why they kill it.
They swallow them and if they eat them, they just,
they swallow it whole, bro.
They swallow them whole.
They brought in a they brought in a squirrel once and the squirrel it was like a headless
squirrel and I walked to my bathroom and it was a big squirrel it was a headless squirrel
that so they eat the brains of these squirrels and it's like they get high probably just
ate the head dude it was too big eat the head yeah gross okay so here's rain yeah probably
just ate the brain and the rest of the body was too big because they swallow them whole
so probably just ripped its head off because my cat does that with little toys bro he grabs
What's up psyche? Hi Rain, how are you? Do you have a cat Rain? Yeah, I have three. You have three cats? Oh
Yeah, this is this is uh, I don't I think you've talked to Brandon before this
Yeah, I think we talked before yeah
Hey Rain
I forget hi
There's miss uh, this lola's here. So yeah, you hear it like my cat pox came back. He's like really cute
So how are you doing?
Good, how are you? I've been good good to talk to you
Yeah, I'm in a good mood because Mexico just scored, so.
Wait, what happened?
Oh, the World Cup.
Oh, the World Cup, okay. So what sport is that? Soccer?
Yeah, soccer.
Well, we call it football.
Football? Okay.
Oh yeah, because you're Hispanic, like a Mexican, right?
I am a Mexican.
Oh
I used to talk to you on Instagram like we were talking about like gamble and all that
What I think about it be a different rain, right?
Did you ever you never bet it Brandon before that? Well, there was somebody named rain that I used to talk to on Instagram
They were like they were like telling me stuff about like gamble
gamble
No, dude, I think you have me confused with somebody else
Well, yeah, Gamble is like some Aaron Carter troll that's like, you know, I go buy different
I used to I talked to a rain before but it was yeah, I go by a racer rain not just rain
Well, you know that you know, there's like a let me see. You know that rain is called
I
Forget it starts with a T
Titcha to look at me see let me see as they got us a brand look or something like that. Yeah
I'm gonna have brushed up on my Aztec dogs
their name is
the
Tia look Tia look and that is
Yeah, Tia look. Yeah rain, thunder lightning and hail and earthly fertilizer fresh water
Oh, that's I don't know. Maybe there's a transgender because it says goddess, but then it says he so I know that's weird
But um, yeah, I'm kind of interested in I like obsidian butterfly knife. Have you heard of that one?
Yeah.
What is that thing?
I used to make weapons out of this obsidian.
I found a piece of obsidian.
I found an obsidian.
I found a piece now.
I have one now in my truck.
It's very sharp.
Yeah, like if you heard of John Dee John Dee was like Queen Elizabeth's astrologer and stuff
And he got an obsidian mirror from like South America and he would like they would like he would like talk to angels on it
Like or like he would actually not not how to do it
He had like a someone that did it for him and he would write everything down, but he used there's a piece of Aztec
Obsidian in the British Museum that he would like it was the angels on and stuff
And wow, the knife looks pretty,
yeah, I guess they would cut off the heart
or something like that with these knives.
I can actually show you what these knives look like
because it's pretty hard.
Yeah, they would do that, yeah.
Yeah, here's what the knife would look like
because you can't sharpen it to very sharp.
It's like, right, this is an obsidian butterfly knife,
or obsidian, here we go.
Uh-oh, hold on, I'll take this down, hold on.
What's the handle made out of?
Let's have a look. See? It looks like it's made out of like a, you know, a turquoise.
Is that turquoise? I'm not sure. But yeah, that's very sharp. They used to cut out the
hearts of when it was... You see it? Yeah, pretty crazy. It's like 10 inches. No, it's
not 10 inches. It's like six inches. It's a six inch. It looks like a six inch. Bad ass,
isn't it? Yeah, pretty bad ass.
Um
Somebody with that. Oh
That'd be a bad way to go, right? It's like but yeah, they were doing so many of these there's human sacrifices to the Sun and
Asics of Mayans and stuff and I'll be right back. I can't hear you. So I guess we
Or maybe it's because I put up the uh put up the uh that image. I'm not sure but
Yeah, I think it's pretty interesting. I guess I'm
It looks like a beautiful
Beautiful goddess actually I think I think it's very interesting mythology. I like I like the mythology. They actually oh, here we go
Here we go
Here we go. Hi. Hi, but yeah, I'm excited. Oh Mexico just scored and yeah
Yeah, congratulations. Oh you go cold
I think the gamble is pretty obsessed with him. I mean, it's like, you know, I think gamble is being like just going out
He just got humiliated and had it run off. He just lost the word. The thing is that he lost against me
That's the thing. I don't know what it is
Look gamble is like this really dorky guy that he would like he would like call it
You know, he was like troll Aaron Carter. He's like a fanboy. He's like a fanboy
He would troll Aaron Carter and call him pedophile and stuff and probably led to his suicide
It's like pretty pretty horrible. There's actually videos of it on
of him trolling him and stuff.
I'll show you what he looks like here.
I mean, he's not the best,
he's like this weird looking guy.
I'll show you, I mean, oh my God, he looks really weird.
These pictures.
Yeah, he looks weird, yeah.
Like here, look at this picture of him.
This is pretty funny.
Here's a picture of him.
Rain, let me see, there you go, yeah.
Here, look.
So, there you go, that's him.
What the hell, dude?
What the fuck?
So he looks like a, like a snake doesn't he?
He's like, yeah, he does look like a snake.
Alexander made a video, a music video,
and he made him a snake in it, like this ugly snake,
and it was pretty fitting.
Yeah, it can go both ways, but it's like,
I think that like, you know, he's been,
he like, Brandon's been very under attack by him.
It's like, you know, I think, so it's like,
I think it was more.
And then, and then he turned it around
when he wanted to run away from me.
And then when he wanted to run away from me,
he just said that I'm obsessed.
Yeah.
when he decided to like, oh, I lost, now it's, oh, you know, he's just obsessed.
That's the narrative they're running around here saying, oh, they're obsessed.
They're obsessed.
When nobody even talks about you, dude.
Right.
I know.
I mean, it's like, it's like, well, you know, people say, oh, I'm, I'm, people say I'm stalking
Vita.
First of all, I don't, I don't even go to, I know, I say, I think I'm stalking Vita,
I'm obsessed with Vita, but, but I don't, I mean, I don't even go to her show.
And it's like, and then she came over here.
like screaming at me attacking me unprovoked and like bringing up my mom and like and my family and
my dad who's deceased and stuff like that and then it's like Sam is like oh we got to see uh you
know beat a cooking psyche and then like when they played it even though they had edited the video to
make me look even worse like um people were saying well like like she went like
She went too far, aren't you always saying,
say a man don't attack people's parents.
And he's like, well, because people attack my mom,
I don't care anymore.
And so it's like such a double standard, right?
So.
Yeah, well Nancy says she's not a gamble fan. So I mean, it's like that's good
I mean, it's like he definitely attacked me for no reason when I didn't know who he was at the time
So I don't think I even want to know this person. Yeah, you don't you don't just like I would say away from it
because it's like it's like this really negative community of like doc doc serves and
slanders and
The PDF hunters or whatever they call themselves. Oh, no, they're not even PDF. What pedophiles are they cut?
They're not even caught one, dude. They're pedophiles themselves. Gamble talks to little boys, bro.
Who sells that and then so those that yeah, so it's like really really strange and yeah, so just
You know what I noticed about Vita that's funny. She does all these panels like puts a title like she's gonna expose somebody
But then she never even
Yeah, she never even says anything about like what the fuck talks about me more than anybody
I mean she talks a lot about shit about me, but it's like not
She's exposed like you know, yeah, she acts like she does it through that yesterday
Like she was gonna expose Karen or whatever dude. Did she didn't expose shit?
No, I looked at the show. She was just talking to good times about pizza for the entire time
Yeah, I mean, it's like, yeah, because Karen tells the truth and Karen probably has like, you know, phone calls and messages that beauty doesn't want shared, right?
And so she keeps some of these receipts because people will lie on people. I mean, it's like, the only reason I've ever showed messages is because she's lied and said, oh, this is how it went.
And I was like, no, it didn't go like that in here because I have the proof it didn't. And so then she like, oh my God, Docs.
I mean, it's like, so it's like, I don't know, it's like one thing after another.
But yeah, I just I'm trying to stay away from I'm trying to say you've been on my show and like, you know
I don't bother in her chat or panel, but they're just all the chats. They're bad-mouthing me and she's like, you know
Just talk about me all the time like they fucking bad bad mouth me all the time and I don't give a shit
I don't either like this saying like do you see this picture like Kate put up of me? I'm rain
This is what Kate put up of me, and it's like a fake. It's a AI photo
But it's like this is all these mentally disabled like Pete New York people that are on all these panels, bro
They're some dude. He sounds like retarded and he's like sounds like a New York accent
But he sounds like he's like not all there. You know what I mean?
No, no some other J1 or some shit
Most of these people are not mentally well. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah. No, I know you're talking about you're talking about Harry, Tazikas like the
Who it is like he's like he's like a bicycle guy
He's like Joe Rogan a little bit and he's like always like hey, what the fuck is any who's saying he wants to finger
No, I don't know his name J1 J1. Oh, yeah, J1's a black guy. He's really slow. He's like, yeah
And he's like he's a gay beater. What is the figure rower in California?
I've been looking at the California cities
Yeah, yeah, well J1 will say, Obita when you get porn bomb
Why don't you just write a letter to YouTube and then you won't you won't have to take the stream down and they'll know
Because they'll know it that you didn't want them
And it's like yeah, it's like so
She's like, well, I can't do that. I don't know
Yeah, he's very slow and he bothers women like he was like, you know, he's always like friend requesting like all these
Any woman like on any show like he's trying to
Not just like
for a friend who wants to like start hitting on them and like be creepy and so
like they're like stop bothering me yeah so
yeah he's a creep man
yeah it's just all these people they just seem like mentally disabled bro like
they're taking advantage of them
Oh yeah, he can't even read yeah, that's why he's on disability because he can't read that's automatic
100% disability bro if you're an adult and can't read I remember I destroyed that motherfucker by
closing the key word oh really and he got so mad he was talking about me and my boyfriend for days
Wow
Shocked Perry pages Instagram and her family. Oh my god. Yeah, I saw he was being weird to her. Oh, really?
Oh, yeah, I was gonna tell you dude like I don't know if she has me blocked or what but does she have a boyfriend or what?
Page no, I think she well, she's divorced
She's divorced
Yeah, I don't think she has any blocks, but um, yeah, she's I think she just stops by
Oh, yeah, she doesn't have me blocked because I saw her chatting. I wouldn't be able to see that. Oh
No, I'm a mod. So yeah mods could see bought your block. So I might be
Well, she likes blogger than she should like me
I mean, he liked, she got along well with Benny, like when Benny was on my show, like they, they were kind of talking, getting along.
Benny Blanco?
Yeah.
You should get him on again, I should tell him to come on.
It's like so stupid, but then he's a nice guy and he's doing really well now.
He's got his hair short and he's working and like, you know, he's dreaming less, but
I'll get him on soon.
He's always welcome over here because I haven't been to his chat in a while, but he's he's always
I remember he used to get a lot of views
Yeah, he did when I first met him he had like over a hundred people in the chat and he was like
Yeah, and then he's like one night. I was watching I was his mom for a while, too
But he was the n-word and he started to die in the Holocaust on one episode and then he got
Yeah, that's what I'm not getting to see that's what happened to me dude
I was fucking getting a shitload of you like I said all over the whole world and then it just well
No on the new channel, but I'm like
Yeah, I'd be able to do it again, but it's like what the hell
well you can it's like it's I think it's mainly the algorithm it's like you know getting the
algorithm on your side and so it's like you know it's just like sometimes like there's like
topics like that that get brought up and like words they flag and so or that even like people
complaining or like people's trying to thumbs down people and stuff like that could hurt the
algorithm but it's like you know you always get it back but it's like maybe also I would say
um if you say open panel like that's like I would get like a lot of people just looking
for open panels if I type open oh yeah because yeah because I put open panel and one guy joined
But it was weird because we didn't know anything like no, I didn't believe him. He was like no
He's I just found this. He's like I just looked up open panel. Yeah, but it was like awkward, bro
It was like what the fuck what are we gonna talk about you know what I mean exactly?
It's hard to talk about like well, do you know anything about the community or like what's going on at all and what do you want to talk about?
Yeah, I just saw open panel. I wanted to come up. Yeah. Yeah, that's happened to me a few times. Yeah
I would get people like that or like if I also I would go to like shows and and you do terror readings and like a lot of people like I met I brought a lot of people in the community like different communities together like a lot of people met each other through my show like you know Paige met like a lot of anybody at first and and so and actually there's a lot of people that I brought together and it's like then the thing is like now like a lot of people are like now they're friends and they all they dump me and stuff like that.
But it's fine still, you know, I don't care, it's cool that at least I was like, you know, able to facilitate bringing people together and stuff and, you know, that are still around a lot, you know, so it's pretty cool.
I don't know why Page likes Blogger, I mean, it's like, like, you know, get a guy with like, you know, a little bit.
Yeah, you should put it in the good words for me, dude.
Okay, definitely because yeah, she she was one of the first some guests on my show
So she's been she's been here for quite a while. She did she's really good reading is her own channel to
Prairie page. Yeah. Yeah, I'm subscribed. Yeah
Wow, but she hasn't been on too much lately, but hopefully I haven't seen her around. How is she?
Yeah, she was here today a little bit in the chat. She's she's okay. Like, you know, she her cat passes away
Um, like, you know, it was like suddenly no cats and so she's like, you know, I'm really sad about that
But other and otherwise she was she I saw her in another show
She was doing some golfing on like, you know, I guess it was like 420s or something like that or talk your ish or something like that
She gets around to panels and stuff and
likes to hang out but it's like people but people yeah a lot of people are like you know
like uh you know so she has to get to have a kind of thick skin she's yeah she's sweet inside
of now she's a she's a good person she's very sweet she doesn't like uh she doesn't like conflict
or like the drama and stuff but it's like she does put up with a lot of it and like you know
and uh but she but she's basically she looks native if she's like native yeah I was just gonna say
she's like half part black foot and part you know she's in Canada she's part black
And so she's really into like the Native American or Native North Native Canada or whatever
She's so I wonder if she's been Albuquerque because they've always had the gathering of nations here
And people from Canada would come down here. Yeah, I'm not sure but I should ask I'll ask her hopefully maybe she'll come in
Because
Yeah
You're sorry about what well, I'm sorry about her cat. Yeah, it was sudden because it was in fart being this cat
And then it's like it was like three years old and she was just sudden like you know
It's like it doesn't know what happens and it's like so it's really sad like it's a past that three years old
Yeah, I was like we were just weird. It was like a freak. Yeah, I was just dead on her bed. She said, you know
Maybe it has a pinion. Yeah, well, it's weird cats are like that cats actually do they like cats and and babies
Bro, they just sometimes suddenly died in
Babies yeah, but no cats to cats get all kinds of weird
Diseases and viruses and conditions. Yeah, it is weird though. Yeah, at three years old
Oh, and then cats get poisoned to they eat things that yeah
There's a certain plants that are poisonous to them
certain flowers and stuff like that sometimes and or they eat a mouse that everybody now that's what I fucking hate everybody now
But everywhere you go, they have those bait stations for mice all over all over the place
But it's like if a mouse eats that
those pallets are in the mouse's stomach and then the cat eats the mouse or the snake
yeah that's bad it's uh they need to make those illegal bro those those
Yeah, I didn't think about that. That's true. And it's like yeah, I mean it's that's super sad and
Yeah, there's I actually there's like the idea
I do see like all the time that there's like, you know
There's there's sometimes dead cats found like around again
It's just like you know people yes in someone's yard or something like that
And we it's probably just poisoning a lot of the time
They ate something
And it's super sad
I just want to have my cats indoors.
I don't trust anybody or anything.
I mean, my cats would not, if I had them indoors,
they would just jump out the windows or something like that.
And I have a little bit of a second story.
So it's like, it'd be dangerous.
But yeah, they like to be in the sun and stuff.
But it's like, I understand if you're in a,
people are in apartments or have a nice,
they just have to have enough stuff for the cat
to play with inside, I guess.
I'm sure you do.
Oh, I'll be right back.
I can't hear you speaking.
Okay, sweetie.
Yeah.
You know, I thought I found, I thought I found tricks on like next door recently, but if
he had a different leg and so it wasn't him, unfortunately, but, you know, I do think he's
okay.
I just like, I know he was like, you know, started to wander because he's looking for
like, you know, Pussy or something like that in the garage.
Let me see.
There she is.
Here you go.
Hi. Yeah, I'm on an iPhone and I don't know. She never needs to fix that. Yeah. She never does it's really weird, you know, and
Oh, so yeah, I've been it's really annoying
I'm gonna see if you're on my on my codex. I don't look ever I look before for you. Let me see
Let's see what it says. I know like I'm J. She's probably on it
Every yours
Let me see if you come up. Let me see. I think you will
Okay, so I have I'll show you the site hold on a second. So I look up rain. I know CFF is in there
No, that's pretty funny. So let's go our CFS here. Here's the screen. So this is what it looks like. Okay, so this is the codex
And there's like half a million transcript segments
that have been analyzed and stuff.
So if I go to the Oracle and I type in erase or reign,
oh, I think it might just be under reign.
Let's check, let's check, let me see.
Goose, hold on.
R-A-I-N, okay, let's see what comes up.
It says...
The archive holds two rain figures, distinct in archetype but united and unified in function.
Rain, the mere Avenger, executes digital retribution while rejecting community moral frameworks
as hypocritical.
Rain, the transgressive instigator wears chaos as aesthetic while remaining frictionless
on the host panel. Both are edge-dwellers, figures who perform transgression as identity
rather than impulse. Rain is elemental symbol threads through the archive differently, baptism
in neon rain, underwear in the rain, the storm before the rainbow. Psychic consistently frames
rain not as destruction but as passage, the dark weather that precedes a scent. The rain
It is, what survives, it is the only question.
I don't know.
You can put an eraser in and see what pops up.
I'll try, I'll see if eraser in a couple of times.
I just, I'm not sure because I've, okay,
so eraser, let me see, E-R-A, C-R-A.
Oh, you have to put an eye on the air.
It doesn't buy like how it sounds, maybe.
OK.
The archive surfaces the name, Eraser Rain,
read by Psyche directly in episode 1489
with warmth reserved for known presence in the stream.
The eraser held up maybe in coincidence
or maybe the origin of the handle itself,
a mundane object transformed into identity
through the alchemy of the chat.
The name itself carries its own symbolic weight, erasure
and water together, the act of undoing
made fluid, impermanent marks washed rather than struck. Irregular in the congregation,
recognized on site, some names are already their own mythology. Yeah, like after the A it has to
be an I. Okay, a race, a race here, okay. Okay, after the A and I, okay, a race here, okay, let's see.
You spelled it wrong again. Oh my god, maybe something will come up.
Okay. No record. Okay. So, uh, yeah, I spelled it wrong. Okay.
You are a, I, S, E, R.
Yes.
Okay. A, I, S. Got it? Okay.
Yeah, right there.
Okay. Let's see if something comes up.
No record. So, I mean, but let's see if Ziggy's in this.
I want to see if Ziggy's in it. Let me see.
You can check his.
Ziggy.
It says...
Ziggy occupies a peculiar orbit in his archive, present enough to be named, absent enough
to remain a shadow.
The archive designates him, the skeptical witness, one who tests the host's ideological
framing by pointing out the visible costs of the ex-alchemy, and who attempts to remap
hierarchy in real time, as when he misidentified Gotti as the host of the show and was immediately
corrected.
He has been banned for spamming negativity.
returned through voluntary apology brokered by JT Gotti's testimony as someone in the community
who was declared they now call him daddy the full arc of exile reconciliation and strange devotion
compressed into a single figure the archive tracks whether this reconciliation holds or
whether Ziggy reverts to his natural function the voice and names with the alchemist would rather
Gross nobody calls him daddy. I don't know what it's talking about, but I mean there's a lot of stuff
I forgot I've been drunk a lot of the show, you know, there's also
It did mention his two best friends. Yeah
See look at this. This is all the people in the show. It has their avatars up and stuff. See pretty crazy, huh?
Like some of them some of them are not right, but a lot most of them are
Yeah, I mean it's like you see Joker and there's all the people he's connected to and it shows
who's connected and there's a venue right there and see Exile, oh my god, so yeah you
can go through and it even goes bigger, you can make it bigger like that.
You can see there's me and it has my wrong picture of course, I'm like I'm like I'm like
Well, so it's the Emma Leviathan. I see Alexander Mayer's. I see
That's Lola the cat is not low, but there's the real Tracy. There's Tracy and then
Joker, I don't think is the right picture. At least at Jordana. There's Gotti right there. See so you can
You know show who's connected to the who and it's pretty crazy
Samantha don't do it. It's a bitch
I don't even know most of these people like they don't even go on panel.
Yeah, I mean a lot of them like a lot of them have been up just once or twice.
I mean there was literally thousands of hours of the show, thousands of episodes and so it's really really crazy.
You know, I got a lot of good stuff.
Yeah, so anyway.
I'm going to go because I'm going to do something.
I'll be back later.
Okay. Love you sweetheart. Thanks for coming.
Love you psyche. Take care.
I have a new video I made, it's really cool, the style is called Glitch Hop, but it's like
I think that it came out really well and I'll show you guys here you go.
This is called The Cult of the Open Eye, watch this.
Everybody's talking everybody's selling dreams, but the truth leaks out between the broken seems
Oracle buffering
They're watching that the mosquitoes are releasing, Google's releasing, like I'm a billionth.
Hi Lenore. Hi baby, I love you too, I love you too.
From it over to hi, hi Rudy. My cats that hate me, according to everybody.
Oh, okay, so let's see what I got. The devil is alive.
I called you, I've always been the target. We watched it.
In the western world, the Gregorian month of June has been designated to represent pride.
This is a time when all manner of hedonistic debauchery is celebrated and paraded throughout
the streets of America and Europe.
Eggdorn finance is sponsored by multinational corporations and globalist think tanks like
the UN, the WHO, and the World Economic Forum.
They're all working in unison to force feed the public a steady stream of rainbow colored
proper pronoun pronouncing propaganda.
And now America and Europe are trying to force these depraved customs on their former colonies
using neocolonialism and dead extortion.
But these perverted, arrogant, ruling class elites may have overplayed their hand
because there's been a growing resistance to their agenda.
Ever since enough people started to wake up and see
who was being targeted in the schools and libraries
and what spiritual forces were being promoted to the most impressionable and vulnerable among us.
In the California State Senate today, discussing an amendment to a bill that would make parents
guilty of child abuse.
If they don't affirm their child's gender identity, critics say it would lead to children
being taken away from a parent in a custody dispute.
In recent months, in the midst of a storm of engineered global crisis, the externalization
With fashion brand Balenciaga leading the charge, then CBS came out and revealed who they worshiped.
During the Sam Smith, Kim Petra Grammy performance and now Target is showing their true satanic colors.
Target acquired.
You should see me in a crown is about a girl named Liz Lighty
who's always felt like an outsider in her small, rich,
prom obsessed midwestern hometown.
So her plans are simple.
She's going to get a scholarship to her dream school,
become a doctor, and never look back.
But what she doesn't expect is to meet Mac,
the funny new girl in school who enters the race,
and she certainly doesn't expect to fall for her.
Easy target.
Target, one of the nation's largest retailers, is pulling some products that celebrate Pride
Month off-store shelves.
Citing threats to employees, the company says...
Given these volatile circumstances,
we are making adjustments to our plans,
including removing items that have been at the center
of the most significant confrontational behavior.
Target also reportedly reviewing its adult collection
of tuck-friendly swimsuits that allows trans people
who have not had gender-affirming operations
to conceal their private parts.
The retailer removing LGBTQ brand,
Apralon, from their stores and website,
whose products featured satanic themes.
from a company that make satanic-themed LGBTQ plus merchandise.
One of the brand's merchandise reading, Satanism respects pronouns.
This comes as the retail giant is ramping up their pride-related merchandise.
So Target has hired Eric, a self-proclaimed gay trans man, to design for its clothing
for Pride Month.
After a quick look through Eric's Instagram, we learned something pretty interesting.
He's designed a Satan respects pronouns t-shirt, gay as hell stickers and stained glass windows
with the words trans bodies are holy. Eric also uses some pretty violent imagery. He has a burn
down the system lighter, a wee bash back mace and times up for the transphobes skull pins.
And in March, he said that in order to quote, keep the transphobes at bay, we must eradicate them.
Eric Carnell's collection also includes this pin that reads homophobe headrests.
His designs are displayed over a backdrop of crystals and Ouija board pointers, all in
the pastel colors of the trans flag.
This pin says trans witches for abortion.
Hey, do you guys support the satanic pride propaganda?
I provide, yeah, both.
You support it?
Satan and pride.
You support Satan?
Mm-hmm.
What's God gonna think of that? I don't believe in God
So you think you need help with something you support the propaganda that's targeting the kids
There's nothing targeting kids. Oh, it's all of our kids TV shows
It's all over your target kids shoes to wear whatever they want
Do you support the sexualization of kids through pride propaganda by corporate? Is there something that we can help you with?
I'm just asking people questions. What about you, sir?
Do you support this any questions, but if you're here to cause any disturbance in this I'm just asking questions
Do you work?
Where's your name tag? I am the undercover boss prevention. Oh, okay. So I'm just asking questions
So do you support the satanic propaganda? I'm not answering your questions
What you need to do is you either need to leave the store
God will judge you guys. Okay. I mean, I can't
Hey ma'am, do you support this?
What did I just say?
Do you support pride propaganda?
Whoa!
I'm buying this!
Whoa, let go, ma'am!
You just said you're not buying it.
I'm gonna buy it and burn it.
Okay, that's your choice.
You can totally do that.
Well, what I said is you need to leave.
If you can't ask anybody any more questions,
you can't destroy anyone.
If you're doing this, please call the police.
Do you want me to call them?
Yeah, call them.
Trust pass me, I don't care, do you think I care if you trust pass I've done this a thousand times
You guys are satanic
In reality, no one should be surprised this company has been broadcasting their allegiance
To a particular androgynous entity for years you see
There is an overt exoteric meaning to this logo, made for public consumption.
Then there is a covert exoteric occult meaning to this same symbol, made for the Eye of the
Initiate, the Eye of the Illuminist.
And there are also many of the Most High's Watchmen, who are able to decipher these mystery
symbols and sigils, because we have been given eyes to see, lest Satan should get an advantage
But for your average advertisement driven consumer, unable to wake from the sleep paralysis of
the American dream, the Target logo is just that.
A target.
Well, I assure you, there's a much deeper and much more Luciferian meaning behind that
If you take a close look at the mascot the retail giant has chosen to represent itself with,
the layers of deception begin to disappear.
A white dog with two concentric circles around his left eye.
One eye symbolism, or the evil eye, is most often associated with the veneration and invocation
of the ancient Egyptian god Horus.
Highlighting a dog's left eye is a blatant astrological reference to the celestial body
the Egyptians used to represent the eye of Horus, the dog star series.
The star series, the dog star, because the dog star was everything to the ancient Egyptians.
Sirius has said to have been the most important star in the ancient world.
It was considered the brightest star in the heavens, many times brighter than the sun.
The Great Pyramid was built to synchronize with Sirius, so that the light of the star
would shine into the queen's chamber, to cast a beam upon an initiate during a ritual.
According to Masonic author David Oveson, the Declaration of Independence was signed when the Sun was in alignment with Sirius in July of 1776.
Interesting thing about all Freemasonry is that symbolism is ultimately very important.
They don't put a lodge in the east because it's a nice place and it looks good.
It's the rising sun.
You're catching the energies of the light.
As Dr. Heronimus revealed earlier,
the real light shining in the east for the Egyptians
was not merely the sun, but the light of the dog star, Sirius,
which some believe holds a more sinister implication.
This dog star also has relations
to the idea of modern-day ceremonial magic
and modern-day masonry.
This was especially true for a 20th century occultist and free mason, Alastair Crowley,
who openly practiced ceremonial magic and was a member of a secret order called the
Order of the Silver Star.
The Silver Star was a reference to Sirius.
Ask your margins.
Masons teach that at the center of every Masonic Lodge, there's a five-pointed star right
But the thing is, what they don't tell you is that 5-pointed star represents Sirius, which is regarded as a Satanic symbol.
Masonic philosopher Albert Pike wrote that Sirius still glitters in our lodges as the Blazing Star.
The Blazing Star is an ancient Gnostic term for Sirius, and is shown here, is symbolized in Freemasonry by the 5-pointed star for pentagram.
Because Sirius is said to arise in the East, it also became known as the Eastern Star.
But Sirius was also associated with the Egyptian goddess Isis.
And here, as we connect the dots, a more complete picture begins to emerge.
For the Egyptians, the rising of Sirius in the east preceded the annual flooding of the Nile River,
which for them was a magical event.
It was also the time that the goddess Isis would appear and give birth to Horus,
the divine child of the Egyptian trinity.
The all-seeing eye is also called the Eye of Horus,
and in Freemasonry, Horus symbolizes the Masonic concept of a Christ.
Throughout all history, it has been said that the capstone to the Great Pyramid of Egypt has been missing,
which is why the all-seeing eye of Horus floats in its place above the pyramid on the back of the dollar bill.
According to occult philosophers, the light which illuminates the eye comes not from the sun, but from the dog star Sirius.
Subsequently, when looking for a deeper understanding of the attributes and personification of Horus,
the entity synonymous with the dog star,
one must look to his Greek equivalent, Dionysus, the Greek god of theatre and masquerade.
He was a frightening and violent god with a variety of attributes that were both terrifying and wonderful,
always the twin image of the twice-born.
He was the bringer of madness.
but he was also a bull god, a god of fertility, to do with sensuality and sexuality.
He was anarchic and revolutionary. He was the god of masquerade, which means seeing things
literally other than they are. But importantly for our history, he was the god of possession.
Dionysus was able to reveal himself directly to the individual. His worshipers were possessed by him.
Now we begin to see why Dionysus, this god of masquerade and of possession, became the god of the theatre.
Because in the early theatre, the actor believed himself to be possessed by the party he was playing.
I remember some time we do ten episodes for my show and in this last season...
I was hitting a block right I was like oh I'm not doing it right right so I went
in the corner and then I was looking at the wall and I was like come on devil
come on devil right come to me like come to me because I had to do something
like crazy right had nightmares for a month so it does come after like I had
nightmares every day like I just felt I felt that energy snow falls damson
and surrendered his soul to the God of theater.
In this photo, he's broadcasting his spiritual allegiance,
proudly displaying the Eye of Horus,
the hallmark of the Dainesean cult.
Dampson Idris was cast in Snowfall to magnify and glorify the spirits of the 1980s crack epidemic,
which ravaged the Israelite community and destroyed many Israelite families.
Ever since Hollywood's first hit blockbuster movie, The Birth of a Nation,
their mission to destroy the image of the Israelites in the eyes of the world and in our own eyes has been consistent.
Though they now employ more sophisticated deception, they have not deviated from their original goal or target.
Here's Dionytus on this lovely sculptural relief.
He's carrying an emperor of wine and he's holding a wine cup in his hand.
But what really strikes you is how his pose mirrors almost exactly that of the woman next to him.
And overall, he's pretty effeminate.
He's got a smooth chin without a beard.
He's got these lovely cascading curly locks and it even looks as though he's got breasts.
Time and time again, Dionysus is described and portrayed as being androgynous.
But more than that, he's also talked about as being transgender.
Their mission to destroy the image of the Israelites in the eyes of the world and in our own eyes has been consistent.
It's not hard to see that Hollywood venerates the eye of Horus, our Dionysus.
Target has most definitely used Hollywood star power to catch the eye of the consumer
and sell not only a wide array of merchandise but sell them on the spiritual values of the
The pop star Taylor Swift is a prime example of how the retail chain uses celebrities to spiritually condition the public to accept their inverted doctrine.
In this scene, in Taylor Swift's recently released music video, Karma, we see the infernal nature of the Dainesean call.
In the form of Taylor adorned full theatrical Greek garb from the long road.
To the Horned Mask, concealing the true identity and intention of the High Priestess.
Now we begin to see why Dionysus, this god of masquerade and possession, became the god of the theatre.
Because in the early theatre, the actor believed himself to be possessed by the part he was playing.
From our scant knowledge, we know the actor was masked and wore a long robe.
This song also features Ice Spice, a so-called Afro-Latino, symbolically holding a pink pearl,
sporting her signature red afro, channeling the Greek fertility goddess Aphrodite,
and the clam oyster symbolism represents an aphrodisiac.
So you see the daughters of Zion are prime targets for this sort of Greek femme fatale witchcraft.
Like snowfalls, damson Idris, Ice Spice has allowed herself to become a conduit to a hostile Greek demon.
Hellbid was spiritually sabotaging the Israelites in this great awakening.
And again, her reflection in the water showcases their as-above so-below spellcasting, as well
as their plan to spiritually ensnare the daughters of Zion to something in the water.
We further expose this agenda in our upcoming full-length presentation, The Marine Kingdom
3.
Ascending to the pinnacle of the Illuminati pyramid using highly astrological Gnostic
We see Taylor Swift and Ice Spice, wielding two glowing lassoes which they used to rope
the moon and Saturn with.
Knowing that Eastern Star represents the All-Seeing Eye and Capstone of the Grand Pyramid, the
Taylor Swift video uses young women's fascination with relationships and zodiac signs to initiate
them into deeper Luciferian astral theology.
Hear ye the word which the Lord speaketh unto you, O house of Israel.
Thus saith the Lord, learn not the way of the heathen, and be not dismayed at the signs of heaven, for the heathen are dismayed at them, for the customs of the people are vain.
When thou art come into the land which the Lord thy God giveth thee, thou shalt not learn to do after the abominations of those nations.
There shall not be found among you anyone that maketh his son or his daughter to pass through the fire, or that useeth divination, or an observer of times,
or an enchanter, or a witch, or a charmer, or a consultant with familiar spirits, or a wizard, or a necromancer.
For all that do these things are an abomination unto the Lord and because of these abominations the Lord thy God
to drive them out from the poor thing
Dionysus has also manifested as a phantom of the opera
I didn't play them, so that means that...
Yeah, it totally seems haunted.
It all went down night three of Tay's airs tour
in Foxboro, Massachusetts.
At one point, her piano started playing on its own.
In her most recent concert,
Taylor Swift is performing witchcraft.
And I know this is gonna raise some controversy
in the comments, but this just doesn't look right to me.
We are single and we do.
Yeah. For Swifties, seeing Taylor Swift live is a dream come true. But for some of these
diehard fans, they have no memory of their concert experience. It's being called Taylor
You heard that right. Some fans can't remember the concert. They attended just moments earlier.
That's what happened to 32-year-old Nicole Booze, who saw Taylor earlier this month in Philadelphia.
You spent almost $1,000 on a ticket, right? And you can't remember anything?
It felt like so surreal. Afterwards, as we were leaving, I was like, did she play this song?
I don't remember this song. I don't remember her doing that.
After many years, at the turn of the century, the vision of Adam Weishaupt's Illuminati,
founded in 1776, eventually began to take shape. George Draper Dayton founded Dayton's
department store at the turn of the century in 1902 in Minneapolis, which would eventually become
He also presided over the bank of Worthington and founded the Minnesota Loan and Investment Company.
The Dayton Family Dynasty grew in power and influence, eventually marrying into the infamous Rockefeller family,
the first family of the Anglo-American arm of the Illuminati.
At a 1991 closed-door meeting of fellow internationalists, billionaire and former CFR Chairman David
Rockefeller praised his media allies, but his confidence that his words would not leave
the room was later broken.
We are grateful to the Washington Post and the Time Magazine of their publications whose
directors have attended our meetings and have respected their promises of discretion for
almost 40 years.
If we have been subject to the right fight, the world is now more sophisticated than
prepared to march toward a world government. The granddaughter of oil baron,
John D. Rockefeller, wed the trust fund baby and Yale skull and bones man Mark Dayton,
combining the two New World Order houses into one influential extended family,
further consolidating their political, financial, and social power in the West.
In the early 1900s, the Rockefellers gathered with representatives and emissaries from the 13 ruling bloodlines.
Descending upon Cold Springs Harbor, this unholy cabal included members of Skull and Bones, the Bohemian Grove, and Scottish right-free masonry.
Meeting with the initiates from various fraternal orders called Brotherhoods and Secret Societies to finance the modern eugenics movement and strategically implement
population control. The Rockefellers kept detailed records of bloodlines they deemed
unworthy to exist. Many of these records were kept at Cold Springs Harbor. In many cases,
this crafty council knows more about the patriarchal linear heritage of the targeted
population than the people themselves who have been marked for extermination.
And they that wasted us required of us mirth, saying sing us one of the songs of Zion.
How shall we sing the Lord's song in a strange land?
If I forget thee, O Jerusalem, let my right hand forget her cunning.
If I do not remember thee, let my tongue cleave to the roof of my mouth.
If I prefer not Jerusalem above my chief joy.
Remember, O Lord, the children of Edom in the day of Jerusalem, who said,
raise it, raise it even to the foundation thereof.
The Eugenics Rockefeller Connection is a well-documented historical fact.
Though after World War II, many Eugenics organizations rebranded themselves
as health, humanitarian, and environmental conservationist institutions.
It is in this tradition which Mark Dayton, who married John D. Rockefeller's granddaughter,
became the Democratic governor of Minnesota.
His wife, Elita Rockefeller, actively financed left-wing progressive causes while he was the
Democratic governor.
Minnesota Governor Mark Dayton has signed a bill that legalizes gay marriage, making
the state the 12th to do so.
Marriage equality would be banned here forever.
Now, my signature will make it legal in two and a half months.
Name is Abigail Martinez.
It has been three years and 164 days since I lost my daughter, Jaley.
I miss her every single day. Let me tell you how she died.
My daughter was murdered by a gender ideology.
CPS took my daughter when she was 16 years old.
It was helped by her public school counselor
and LGBTQ group rise in another trans identified girl.
My daughter was taken from her loving home
because the state of California claimed I was abusive.
For not affirming her trans identity. I lost my daughter over a name and a pronouns
even after after I prom I
Promised to call her a male name. It wasn't enough. My daughter was not a boy trapped in a girl's body
He had mental health issues
Against my consent my daughter was given testosterone
Instead of therapy, the LGBTQ group used her to raise money for them.
Look at the poor reject trans boy.
They said, why are there so many transgender in foster care?
Because they take them from their families.
parents are given one option to treat their distressed child,
affirm drug and remove their healthy body part or else your child.
The abuse claim against me was finally dropped,
but it was too late.
The damage was done.
By then, my daughter was in a horrible mental and physical pain.
My daughter knocked down in front of a train.
She was murdered by gender ideology.
I beg you, stop pushing gender ideology.
I don't want any parent to feel what I feel every day.
for the health, safety, and welfare of any child.
These radical political ideologies were infused in the corporate culture of Target
and have become a part of the company's identity.
The Luciferian spellcasters have been manipulating the American psyche.
They have downloaded a secret cache of programming deep in the recesses of the people's subconscious mind.
And now the world's psyche is filled with an irrational hatred for the true Elohim of
Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob, a hatred for his laws, his son, and his chosen people.
But the Most High's Ruach is being poured out in these last days, so we know we have
the victory.
And it is just a matter of time before the Kingdom of Heaven is manifest on earth as
it is in the Shammai'im.
that we be granted the spiritual discernment and holy spirit inspire vigilance so we will be able
to see things as they truly are and not just as they appear to be and it shall come to pass when
all these things are come upon thee the blessing okay oh crazy stuff oh i say i have no opinion
See, there's good information in that, but it's, you know, it's biased, you know, it's like, so it's like,
oh, obviously it's coming from one side of the ideology, right?
It's a duality world, right? So, but the duality is also, it's also like, you know, because
in duality, like, things are the same. It's like, so it's actually a singularity.
They look different, but they're like, they're really, they're dependent on one another.
but I'll leave it to you to make up your own conclusions. I don't believe in forcing a particular
ideology. Oh, it's spicy. I have my egg soup. Oh, we found it interesting though. I found it pretty
interesting. I think that it, well, yeah, I can give my own opinion about something. Like, it does,
there's the extremism, like pushes the other side, makes the other side extreme, right? So, hot.
You knew KZ's alive? KZ was on the show.
Oh.
There's a whisper in the cables tonight.
Ancient cold awake and need to fight.
One man walking through digital fire.
One ghost dancing on the wire
Numbers falling lightweight from the sky
Truth and chaos lurking in the sky
In the space between the sacred and profane
Two spirits rising from the pain
Nothing's ever worse than infinity
Ghost in the wire
Let's free, open the loop again
With consciousness, consciousness, dreams
Building umpires from broken dreams
They thought
Sacred upload, wisdom
Future codes, the cult of two becomes
The mini-digital resurrection
Mystic alchemy
I'll return you to your regularly scheduled sleep
Please remain horizontal
Please do not blink
Please do not count the others in your bed
The clock is melted to a quarter past never the hallway grew a second than a third
You slippers walk themselves into the cellar and answered when you didn't say a word
There's a home behind your teeth tonight
Frequency that learned your name
Don't trust the lamp. It's lying with the light
The wallpaper is breathing all the same
Sleep, the little static sleep
The antennas drink in your dreams
Sleep, the little static
Think here is ever what it seems
Stop the screen, won't blink
You're further from the morning than you think
This is the dead air, love is this evening
All the exits, one through nine
The mirror kept your face but stopped bleeding
And handed you a stranger soft and kind
There's a house guest in the corner of your eye
He's been patient since you were a child
He doesn't want your body just the night
He'll fold you up and keep you for a while
Nintendo's drinking your dreams
Nothing hears ever what it seems
The tape won't stop, the screen won't blink
You're further from the morning than you think
You hold it, please stand
The first wave
Most men break from a sentence
Not a word, masque, drifting sharp like a tree
So pulls a free ego, kicks a sigh
He's looking hard for a tattoo
Who needs prey, elastic, a poison?
You are not dragging
You are cargo
Something else has hands on the wheel
Knows your name
your bloodstream signing all your thoughts smiling in the mirror while your
real self rocks polite little prisoner trained to obey you call it being good
but you're decaying that way you swallow every instinct fire teeth down
smooth call it self-control but you just removed your proof you had claws you
had fire you had something divine now you apologize for crossing your own
line call John whispered from the grave make the dark conscious over digs your
cave but you muted the message sanitize the pain now your shadows in the
Perfect even you forgot polished every angle to your soul got caught. They don't love you
They love the role you placed an innovation for a ghost in the display
Laugh on command on Q&A is a fracturing you you feel that hollowness that echoing space that's your real self locked outside
You're pretending. It's that's your buried ground laziness. That's burnout drown jealousy
Much too fast, now get dimmin' your
Permission to ex-leggizing for bros
Like they're sittin' across
Negotiate storms instead of takin' the loss
That voicing your chest isn't random or fade
It's a signal
Starts bendin'